[{"topicId":"14","id":"14000","langCode":"vi","question":"OBmbgF/o/bNq3ZHSrL62zA65mBhrV+0O32yAlVy0c+raC+57DOq9ZI39/G368IeI","answers":["both","so","yet","but"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7zhbUmIrJfPFWBX/EHuRvgYvm3sjJ4ZAEYsGPrbJHU3VLoTjF6BjY70/XoYW0g/Prz9WT9m8YlvyAwW/5mUXnWB2tkxqh6EUqF8rgDDKrY03ItxLrnXie3naog2Tj4lT+/Y/Yq0x/xkmYFvyqfFuX/DeacDleWC/l4zjMfSqbxdbtRu2hOUh5GBeNiX3IxKO+91qGYWyID7h0vm1IC44aQVoUKtSQ4unSQ8fjyNrEprZ/Unh50TZ7Nf5N2k3SRyFzY3TzSIPobGc94PoRxUudcEhsO/GXFU81uLIjLQc4r7y3o58iLJrmU3ZLLS+tsZ2RYcjH2ccV4m6GMhj4AZQYHrL3L20soJE1jz4qZHztD+qeLjJFqqmVpRLxt0Pw3YSTiBlGmaTQ5RCR3hYs58mi6DPwQ29/4YJe+YZH5aP6aV42jlkXLbPFp7eO5qAEh9B6/z5adkgpfAqqjni17CvQjfb4pjNfHPHyqsEvgWPuVLYknZ5MjTXkyTfWy6KiJd3oo6VDy257hc6cst/51qMYBit5/GPjIb/DQ+/cydG1nl808F/VlSdZR80E0wskuyndVRZyjlZmVrarYosuFIXTLXRaJQlmGPWGa9eZqh/+eI6p/9c1kt65gEMhfb6yrWnNg2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF28Z5FzWtxFPL+Fv+DB9Jzqc33uxokdAcqnaKW9R32GhNit15jxv/KXj9J3/trDZpQwpcNMWUJGFWEAeXhMsBifGGue3lIK2I0OtKJwoRrOky4ohEU5jPS8xiiis1PUr2Vo\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14001","langCode":"vi","question":"/dOp/JBtoSdA4r9w40fWUZn03civ+PSKG3bi3uaq+E1UmJqZlUmvnixdweKSD73TzHds2CUGmsWhgGaed+jTXqw+5AZcELkrvfdvWbAr1+u23ZGDX/IZqytgG2EMmmGxfKxQZK1HiIGuAuzgIwgNZ3UlYL2R2VHhywedijF+VXY0hNcWM6MBoN5TvmIa4WF1Q4gaX/7PQmZ4q58uHeXDfw\u003d\u003d","answers":["before","and","yet","but"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE65Nm7CkV6KsBDiXI82WKPYBefj0b/lTn0/1VGj9ojFKM97UYsRgB5I6LBbEPxnRrOnYF+gKndESyy9mWxLsn0SkZi54wy5e+GXpQO3P+3D0/8eZZ7duXPJKYdHwdifdzq98XUfszbGoJM1WirPUv7TW73CMAeWtPnltA6gLhjGhWQc2V3LLOs09VMFuN0Eq6vdIeqD0yA9qiElSI9RM+QNPQIfKnnB3noHtOg61xLDg8Dfb9iKBzwJwllvSgSEHNjNKzZHtjqUuM5ej7VDCRESyMNHnG8g11HcSV8lWqNYbtsJ065hltT3URZY3EGVy799ZXqY8wPGasBB+WgRPRgGmSn1m4Kb6vRuNqVrBIfwdQr3DY8jK00tIv49aKutxH8gM74eMu/i7OmFNl5kc6ACB4UXb2dDneHJvk32jyV3gOWFhMt0XCDHn5NWFsZ2eqwIgZbPEa4g2vC9DF+38L4G49pi2mhHeaIUuKSRo6TlELx84Xuwcqn7MMj26lYXEAa6su62aAfJwVsS7nwsBbLkOFPE+NNI0WTTLARGqqJp9mbqf9JLYwG0yNdfloxKDXx9tI7tNk3jnyRgglZBLWkgntGb8J3+rSjNICL8uXlGwPWGN7PQe2F9GdotS+LnhktzKYVmF93wkHB4BZSOt8f4rSGGNhh4OUH5504Zy3YrrOJOoN/gWAjbINou7get5/gwj7HR7yZEj55+dyRElxrIe84Ry8JYw6ihRb53fyqNvw9HZV6NoMgwOnplwXIXrWEo1yQWRILA1A+EVTMCRc7oO/jh7oSBhNBjRMMReuyN4nMoLhgZOTiHWiS0KrVGJ+yZ8GBtCOGQab6zVokQII6E\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14002","langCode":"vi","question":"WWWL8zjnz2NBMnQvTeCM6Eb+qY2NMxxILyrDaedUuF6t0UNYn+YPAOduUABdI91EFq1LyGCs6BnXGgX6iOwG/qvyGT/sm9J0/b5KZhV3qMLmEqwRnbWjXxkDhkfcw5tDlnCQakyNb3rHTsVbEJ9qfA\u003d\u003d","answers":["but","or","for","so"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5BnaqaqmKcp64lfXenRRkO9stCrqXQof6EmbBtSdeoqVXkzOpktLC748cKMRDcBnQdoKbVoqqpYb3GNgQoqMZ22h1iiqaTYKVyj7khBSgB9ltTGGIAuKysJ5I4syJRznVSSYJySf3AqT0qxkAITcfwhcnxNX2PteMnLckUQlKi0LwF8P5K0G8MD43ll/z0SNcMDjRlHO+HgfxaTY9JWvXyWhAP2X2jBPR9j23UAePdlY1jXU9PwMWX9cGr7I74K5TdNu/8zaMITRI3CbrtVYSMWeG7POEaX5XD4Quuqrm/9q/RrfnEkXOIXY5BnZIGf4UiXS6Rs9QB0NEjKMGY1qi9jjm1rIHOC49CmPS0+lHB673DJ27pGI869YgwovzDd39g2Om8lGxdiuacuzySSF2+vnSb4ix1ldh0PHrP5BshYlzedd91EPGLspf+gXF2fneWq+dITpJ5MS9wE2zNz/JT+R7YnDtF9eO536yYuqJ01X9JoAorYDsNPTE9vN68kU94VY/Tq8ATAGGOnrgX5gLXXvwhr8JvZHRkOCruH4oEI0SPwfaC2gpp2ykfHJWS5PPPTuqZU3Z50nhZ3L2P+W9ljO31EzB4nKp0lvyYGyJV60oBKrZlh5aICufpS8GJ/+klRR6OI88lDDNKSErtrfZhYLojo9b2Uv9WUvBUw5DCfhKeHOcUAEOSVI2MEuEZSCCObTT1gM2rYOrYO8XDs7BzPfAf4hzOGyqn1GfEdy8KTc1P/w9CtDR5BRc6grKjpfdXz16H7ANB+EDJfyUzTHhWQhbUHFBpW8qWWx0LYWSR2VpZ8ZksjJA1eHNcfuuNZLRxLSUUta5o+B09ap6VRlnah8/Pv+4lsMtfeHV14uQGZyLnNettP6w1iFjjBGAmDvInef+ynT6oVKAVQ63PrPcBMz/U0rBBP2BaZWvBqNatuuCBqGpf4uC8/WHGyrRAjVdt22DlPnDpn0A44N9SFPzraNkynqrbfuevOkH3p1Cz9"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14003","langCode":"vi","question":"kSvbtXAGtq9LMxoef2q6meecuXqBS5h9VtuIb0s5v77rv7rodKCFshzTz9k+rPpBrGlrofr0I2ldRcMIAF7Trw\u003d\u003d","answers":["so","yet","or","for"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6w8pIUKZbxapaY2fN+ou9G0AFLX6Aljywd4WrnR+11ZydcJa0UTQzULKywaBZKJc2xp5ee3uGRi8YCfjh+sS1IhbPkI8AwYe6L8apc9B7QP4EgLQuPmxTMBMKhV3rCZfJWVged1Q1ZBgiftEkkp+Ehv6CmiEqpB9aarAjSiANFCCsF16G0RtGd7Xnuu06HpPs/1dWAOx6g5AdPUJR0ZsMMQqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjdlhtLrY/vCyNbYcph++olQ26qKrpQ3aNrLS6huUuw9v4bKPiwo8WyITJjoso6dwAIGuxm5SufCTqLY0eG54LGEf2JqG2BAEnlcTvNhWZajulm3rIU+D9BLib2aU73jvs0yEIutyxKPPODGGHFdETD7PfAf4hzOGyqn1GfEdy8KTc1P/w9CtDR5BRc6grKjpfdXz16H7ANB+EDJfyUzTHhWQhbUHFBpW8qWWx0LYWSR2VpZ8ZksjJA1eHNcfuuNZLRxLSUUta5o+B09ap6VRlnah8/Pv+4lsMtfeHV14uQGZyLnNettP6w1iFjjBGAmDvInef+ynT6oVKAVQ63PrPcBMz/U0rBBP2BaZWvBqNatuuCBqGpf4uC8/WHGyrRAjVdt22DlPnDpn0A44N9SFPzqP4LervlZdCWA6+V/9iu5ockxfZ0AXBxLEJn7cyPzsc70f309+6Y6+ThD/QePyEwBzJsBiXZaGrA+GZXOQ7Jeov0Xo96NaK8H6FaH02nyCWg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14004","langCode":"vi","question":"CT5JVr6JpUa7N0/xn1/gkrHCG8PA06nnRq1BeytM7Uc4OqteWUAm9wa+QO5gqSApfb+ILnyytRHw2uHuJnkbkw\u003d\u003d","answers":["for","nor","so","but"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3CcAl5tWrxeIYezOqN05h/e4OLSng+CQ7nZrQt5I0qyAppiWEt2v/m18VhmVtjVQxH/13mMDIuuOT69JNACVu6tAQ9CY9konmhtXYhnWSoycJ2o1oVmpNGAMveyzXJ5vrIREtX8ZdbsUYLLchp2XMpQio+uYHZ+yD7TrwIOM5wr35YxYGNAH7Yt86w/N3jyupHGXwHmcaRLa+M0EakayRFpnFOzttD727v0pycdazTaMMj7iR1q2+nHsTeDeU1yYRnTRZHX6+UFSbbmeLSZTtYFvJ+QHyK/91EhLFsT59ipQXVNhXJiE6VAzdoJHjXN56ISTu1wufMLmH2LG5ZBUycACd0OCW7iALxaixCfzbu2Rv/OItFzjwOjoHY1TesQrui6wHCNSd7Wl0ZFB04dtWrHZOzCgn6CNYSc0mZBvZJMSNrO3fZXCbfji+p2hnI9bZxOMMSX5q8AXqGlF9Sd3b+Sy4KVC/Y6iPYIpnM9w92DDAU7CjC+AW/gTIAqnehdrb21V/SOwc2v5oDr0q2/HsGlubk0P7/gSjhDpszwbWI0eJnsJFBnBu1dbDtJu9sXMNgndt1HwdCT1bN1DS60KlRd9ls0qJdM0hYDeSZiWJSiS8fVFsiVUfuu8yJBxTm5HIOKZdilnBlr07kuDlTqXew\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14005","langCode":"vi","question":"Jn+dGFW8yKF6tAs7I3TEaGOmqlD3ms6V/DEAASGmwo0+cxQAON8iqozmU1nOfXc5ddpDJ/QonEEv5gMAeU4tEw\u003d\u003d","answers":["but","for","so","or"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+WdTJFeWbdpmHI+aAlOmC+YtUD1D818jqCU87YVdR+DGz2dc7VYR07Fqz4lEOy191uSLoy3RQIHVQ+3PfPaL7aPTr44qmPWI3kZnszA4D71oNG0lkcoeASDHw8IiqchaYykxbKfo7yhRNGAA8kfHiNu/KgGLYqJkxZm0HvKbLnwyToYAQc3Q4N61U0dj2JsQYYzBgRPCGRPVS4Lty1NrvL9OL7wUgsu2XGNdEATVTQqT0CHyp5wd56B7ToOtcSw4G7UlJUh1QpdHfzoMCQQIKjwjC70ENaxFPwgU88AYFwepalIx3qeC8INmJI9nH9zzeG1aKAi+jANhJOWoTTLfmWtdFgXsc0zxoW08YoUr4g5KFvcBopTysC5bWJ8OKEqbMW/MvsEZwWKWEo45BjHZx4e84Ry8JYw6ihRb53fyqNvEDtnNEJIzIVfh5aKUm23p8eZ2oYy90NZQgOEBfqJYSCgWlubtvjIz9SzNkgiN5cAmOa2n+PQhmj7scLlcPyPoqhbsFf9wUQfRnuB6BYSyWC5aaTxy/Nf8Yim/j9nCsdIwnMp+TQvtbi1wsQn4eBh4cnRxPPdWz34sq35lotz+rfdaE7QPYf04ybQYYom8mF9JLaQoLMqoNHqpGT8SzPL2OFaDyiYVwBlA6CeMoNpeoE\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14006","langCode":"vi","question":"HgH2MGEF8XXiNcvy9F0H0Owv6/hHF6Xt5kst9tWEu5lPWQNuyPiKaBZFBnagTr6/cUHtSjZUkubxx3X1DCd221SAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["but","yet","so","and"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5PoS3raCt2kO1k57+p6Yp28VMqyMbCbHtppqvIMk+PTqBgup++jaoiBxw4+Qhpmfmc3fcG3l++DnR1ea8vAa2H9QXh8JP+bF4f7Rc3xA1mkibi2+KNnO+O6gGtR9hsshiVSbDwssXLCm3rrbapjUV80rhlLohSprAablB7P2IrsoV47O+b9opvGUuOy1F9kl292BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30xsgJ2mXfwy7pvKP1Lymbss2PfdiqT0FDHn1SQJyVIa3HHC7hrK/51jIQQ3sQN2iWS/Lzd09uyYobaRddmKVvBgQhTLKm5fre3hLMKLzVQyyMpIlBC9HbHsqpO+QID3H04OeanLlPicmgNzkVoB7DOk4gVR4tQeA7VgwiS0pn/qIycn19hntJ4VHe8tv98NBthNA5eXB8wMgXgMSfY+w54hQbF6CqXohCCJDzCSiz9KiRe/A9++v23P22QBWCDSPvDXINQKHhcz0LVBbRNKcg/WHv5fFd5pXp57SmNcwC7roOPDD3KMdoidpCAmLXv6SLnih8Yx32O7p6N7mv1Wal4mivRq0zob1giE2HFqqpzKkify3hwsDED8/7sEFTz2AdmJ7eh29yXcLW7b+tadxiRwPMe2aCpFQYye1J2UJDW0655wc1/GfVh/TqRwfRNnncozCw6DwImq+ADysRrrAGZBeoHBuNAwUWAauuSkft7VfzmaYH1cqOvK9AVruISuLwmsgfWooBIHq2WVfIlLP2micu2p5g9knoTzgs4WdY6L7cD3UK6LnwEHtLnxLREZ2XrrL3L20soJE1jz4qZHztD+qeLjJFqqmVpRLxt0Pw3YSTiBlGmaTQ5RCR3hYs58mi4W2Lv2d3W1EPp8x04p3Amncv/+h0OAADbCyk7Vjxg+2sgh2rSTIrJFlWENC0HfFnn2AW8Cji5ITSnPChIuF/NW"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14007","langCode":"vi","question":"j4PpK7/U+A5n2atxKm94zRM7d1ZViOkyipPKhPGfm6vEXHooJIY93n9kPR2orOXGRDoDlUkCKH+RDYSdu7yxJw\u003d\u003d","answers":["but","or","yet","so"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzkxJUi5cMWsa4QlAe4pZ4Tlh0b2F5klT0smvFR2HBuGcqr/Hb2k/k+PyUzpmyh23sjHk2yorF32EiQrDnJV0+wHdnuYfg3sI6ev6rEW2j535tEw5hsiL4x0C2beqc1WfahOgCrmDHYTH+HEoh++H3ClQJd3EnsNRV0Ayif1bGYs00lf/R7UeuG8JQZwqDTTz78mDpeg69ZTEUUw3yuX1eOfjHhKv3cu61iT0DlHIGbIDyD0/5uZe0xG8BpTF1ZxTRRuG/oM2C92UQ6QMVrY+FOUEKRFDF4oeaRYOouM/P8rkdKQm48Hj+v49ae6CKVVyxCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HONLS0CWGuF0H3bp/Z2jlmlKp2iyXxzMTgbjg7W8Erv7Zw3mIAkowxbsAiFE9lYv6dvVV8L98unzdce212spFnQBFLz32kV3Ly7hEkDArJPDH6xOF/kXh4BH0zPrLakL5WTCIO4xtS7ddoGpay5GWOZNKJSUjjfWpqL9XnhVejXp0frZcZ6cvbvQa4ovCMfRAO4cfoixY3NOYzeojXmws2vJWCtMa6O4OUTxvQGD+xnZnTmTm8dhsnAaxhGIFEFXHptwGSWYONZ1ywAeskFT/BS4ZqSXFuKND3NGgKLBGszfucb1e46NmVwz7OMRXWrkQd9e8nZ8+fD9dPksFFBS0citeiW0AH11M6uMrP/6ztp2hZ/b6phOokMHQe04cODGe8RNNfLqdUNxeJokPYNoZQpA5xWMyQjUzQRZwMpnlZ+/ipdi476tDnleQfeOZoyxTKcBG4yyTAlaUBT/t+rN+Fo9rhLwM/56e43SrqQXzoIeL8iHQAo0lyspv3lSXrwYr4imF8saytP9UbEAFkRbAo9f0DqEwG4NNprjbE8CPOU0ucV4CtJoWlaSVcDMedRXL4Qoi0lRAxVlamlouwEubbnXQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14008","langCode":"vi","question":"jr94rRdZSzaN55QGhuDHHrMSh0v9/UHVUXK/c1AH4KXMULI4B2zSPLtnhqw5Z2feIaQWOLPrj5cM2e2uJI941GtaFBgEL2p02at2r+m0lHs\u003d","answers":["after","but","although","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwpbn9KQbGuBx5DQpe3gOMW35bZfnRVdgJBBEqX1sm5DFaFCrUkOLp0kPH48jaxKa+KpntXSmo7SsbiQ+89YKpQTZEgcLeZxdqE3sHsUE2CwV1P8dgNVNREgfw4KUcaAtes4ywvId28WlxYpN7kMvsctU9D/tspJ6rPTSxXc1uDgzUIigO9ESGvK2pbMqrQA9HpBf4/EGe33Y26nKnpeTmMxZpcin6f1nA36s0ADC6GUCx1w5CTbLz0jQK22c9/wJJPunseJJHLU0zlT2bTNyAscjvA4U8kzK1xq5BjtF3+o5bq0ezKzadZMoM2EkDryDOj8X6GRT4C0l3R69eSju50Z60IRoJbXFrpXY8MIr0MHcPp+QNM5yAetinl5psRCAw0JHVN1jpe0M0qdi8GlV9vJRmx7M/P2qwGHq8FqUv9ecHzFpzjh/csA2nnmlMCsUIQ35w+gJHLNJHCVADNz3Ey97Q5CPag+COqRvV1+Ghm6LTh07Pd3rtQNcvcLC+BLt61TnoZD8H4uBv5qhbJSm0GBkZTnKuevnrb+Yt3+3eTJ0UoxPJT2qUboCi52b9hmH9KlvBuVju080G5CLhtSW9QaBsS7FJo2HKh4gt2dhWiONx79eLCr9DaZB7zzALErD/rSQvQ0WL3FYEYrSkxdm2ugk80g45QcNB/XByK98FgTDwafHBQovDGMJ5i766Po0TI11KyPEET2ALcBblAuggU9HedqeH6sAJve/wY5zc30sjsBjh/IIV1pwjCvl7JfYDxqu+zYlJv/PP47qR80zPitL7+yNR2Ia5LJQW7ck8/0/wp6SrbtaWS4RyhUntEE2uRVT8m13NIQjkTtHgMMdkvCRG0XwDozuMxTPSjEpBDa+TyF7YksPrvPqNfjyblX84paH0IRbx8UL/gHBLwolxb3cMTkZfWkoqU9FAIF8A/SwvjXGAh4rbTs7V4ZpK3YfYczJHcB4HMMdcj8oy+caLtnfTfziUXpDxERBU/s5ZOVOJgZiRJc+EGvuUlCAGe+TSaEacDjoi+VNhfPmFNKsic\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14009","langCode":"vi","question":"yvTvcMx9d4REPSOraqMJOj8HdEU7eGDqTcF17a2WiqXy0GQjDRDXGJSeQ5+93cxW7WRYfVzfihfWGL5zM8UVWIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["or","although","and","so"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEyuDzRnF1s38vgZzmCTXruWKGXgX6/CJPxPLFelHahlEtKyU/iNLmuoEGHQBADVY6cL41xgIeK207O1eGaSt2H2HMyR3AeBzDHXI/KMvnGi7Z30384lF6Q8REQVP7OWTlTiYGYkSXPhBr7lJQgBnvk3I2Fy6UNl1xSkUYmKmlgAl3NeL9W67g1bRn0h3Z6zaVL0gMJwvxPx0tVWunCRZYUmJW6dHSmqRgMrHfyOzfDJYs9pSsWX1b7P9VnQPMRFKhIxlMDqO6/5Nru0RIb1hRi8MO3LP0CTy4vCCSYo0yPO1h/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8W4Us5opV4oUsdqor+vUkjCSmmXjLtz53iRfRcfhtVLq6TQE/hINT4FdXxqHFEoPAjkQ+ZsrPYoigcpWsCrbktymmHrRTvvKafoOs8ghPhrUA+3oqGEApnQvoeHRZQBjQSRMSwY7w237z1NGekKOajb8f7HLdt57wwEWPV5lW6mgVPYJ3OMMpRIX/tGx9WvAjz5vF7Cq69ZqA4+T1UctbMojmB/hnWVdbUVLl/BKd83a50wf37g93JkkxjPXNFHAIlAiLvUEgJd6bo5wy4lmhyysE9ukvswHWv7O6N5Gc7yaFxaNUehVoKxE2dO03QX6lY6bF1HSx0yb/CFoYJxXcakUcs+Foeinaqc0D4FUHuV9y4nO9gFsagJ39Vx36WA9j9v2zqHKgvVw9sO1rAdgqLjkFU1vHIUVPYwTOfv9ggUDVqfEehCda54jQZTozKvt7GB50CRBQZeHFcyOkpPdWsif6grSJo4sX4uP5P3Ptc2bQEw5TBRxFIycN9DP+p5oy2/sT3EgT1DXp3ZS5dNkcJLY7HdK0yT5U8ubAqFHdqp43ZODSTdNEqfZJDH1nnGxpXNSpZa+HjppB+CVBYttgph8vJHf4bGY8UYRaRzcSXZ8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14010","langCode":"vi","question":"xunZ3UWkEX3HtZHj3W56FTcRIXUSYg8/1e3mQAmFpnZQh8IwEGr/VqfLZqufseO3","answers":["or","although","before","so"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7n8T0OgZAFR5PSoYKN6TlHkd0432PJPped8VlfEhSJbLx84Xuwcqn7MMj26lYXEAZPL2OgZMSZga4c198QryGUSEKl/9RCxoSJzCb9tPheB0e5h7JTKC5sLTVsb9AN81VspsClXkSGoiiNlL2EZPSJx9gjxLrX+dOd/ioDfW7IpwF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/GH7CW/vONhQCL8Kr1QQSz5uauVnngN7bNBLscK10wAd3IvsMAgqL8Co9o1eD/DdEMXkUy6/Dyw68oUr7RLF5KNHgIAhqHsqK1oVHb10xniPh47iaz9CQlX9sMRAyZa9Ry1afwsGBsvyo3GHUe6Ymg/i5fs/NZFX/95lY2qS/3yLRF2Kc6Ww4FrcoeKlNC/HLjRcqBWUsjiC67xuXtloEPxod1kG56PaLMK82EYq0vRphTVhSs80cyPDmGnt6emlEtB3Mhy3nY+ujkXmcjgKVeqbXoKiKDiu9ZAtH6YVUcud3a0FdKEQUwLKAoMWWhPrezX9AKWAuaXOWLR+lTk5Y886CyqaplzEY4JHm2uqy+V9tMGooEmf0Mnn/3JtDIlbPPLg+AKlpTyd6NB30lfc7x+rkxIKpb22dpHMmrWj+4xVJm49AnRC555CSkqWgsWWsxTtQCdzXY0OZCQMqj7KNjbciW2pDg9lHUs7GDuxGJ2xcZdpfHJbK+BSoKJkjAnK3tycztNG4Rvs9OnLU6KdoFbR/+ye/q4+YAggBiN7GJt/2DykWOhePm4mzDx+QI5QtzqeDBaaPHx/ld5gmkWmPuHUqorNVeFkowgHQOuWAtinGdUBQA0Um54Jm8Uibw440I\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14011","langCode":"vi","question":"CoBehqZLpZ5Y3KcthqDStpFELFmX0LzAsGZiwXGURhpDL5z90qmCpb4ojUCqanqFVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["until","or","so","nor"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEwPw/YB85e/2wPz3lwvnO7ANP3UkicP3Czpef4SkGKyTyNgOSVNs8+IuiOYuUaJic3rkexInCyVSqxtEZ4CpoTp+UK+8z72+L7NZsqYa88MlzFxFkxZx7IAuwMo3QIvDW8lGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQUviHXbMj8G+mSeGEPbXsS04nQuUOqxYduO3Z+Z1JLB3LLs4G0GaOVTOPQjhYM9wQHS8Ybj3QO9O8EDnANwUW9vrgkK7EqE85C6nOdFC24N7AxXFFELybXzapdMSIdj4yZn5xZhxx1QgiVCbC7XrRIRv9xlZEKQyna6KQgq5btFwUHcR0C78b4uZ/FvRI2M29ecHUx1FPBACE1GpTS3N3QUloYY02tS6qEuNykPSUAgsnL2dwo3fyUoDeI1BMi15Dl3lKvgeGs2r8Sk4CTgTB8O7wxM8Fj9/+cUDtvDPy70bv8PkRtaLiZ8K6yJyIkW7vggc1ZRUR7LMThn8QXFGk1GjryFwKteOWJsp6IO0gQc5bgaxxtBRB5nLBigiaSrwkSu0/7XMlgDGx1n8JAu1xodtUuVFLWEPONdXhE81grqYFPiW8paEQrUC2y3F2qL8fU+gZnwnoawUcuaqV80rwxBTaM6eXiId/dEpygcgXqwUEqwYjUWD0UDh6OAStrjSyG/5FvG3mrSozTwxL0/EODg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14012","langCode":"vi","question":"H1wSfdq1Sd+aralW5eyhBxdf2zlnewtzJcvsY+LeHGlbv7D/gU00j4IjVQj32i9P1hdt2i/VT7v+/htmzqMBDQttxrQBhDae6Rp1FNuGkLA\u003d","answers":["till","but","yet","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4RiebKDYQn71I65noYv48oiVwbZz9/BkF80T6o28R7TX64LhU5vNt5C8faEeyJcExWhQq1JDi6dJDx+PI2sSmv/+GE9azcsWc89GpFryvNqutRyN3dbrIl7+TKPLNr2MEUnxSwTUO8M0TmXTLp6OGTug9VfQbDSlReG62l2lM59IBuRLAdXwIFFdxALNNbosR9gkXiD8e2JsHgw2anioDke3YlhDW/DQGQ7R/7a9Zs+ORstYgwEK9Uudf/E9Q8WLrbZbZO6vGGAZeMNoThHnALxmNncRLPi0MPAlPAz7JmRStj3nR4fP+/0Bl8KeKT9YhzB+dbZtoPsDcbWvy7TJpsYHcAhVBDCIpsAtVGDEWx6+p15JZlh7urbNfTHExYY5wu29hMVUxTswMf2/Bx2umSFLKcly8Cn0mJF/QcU3CiGGz2dc7VYR07Fqz4lEOy191uSLoy3RQIHVQ+3PfPaL7aPTr44qmPWI3kZnszA4D71oNG0lkcoeASDHw8IiqchaYykxbKfo7yhRNGAA8kfHiNu/KgGLYqJkxZm0HvKbLnwyToYAQc3Q4N61U0dj2JsQYYzBgRPCGRPVS4Lty1NrvLyW1JiivfzCEWnJzZHgvHZydcJa0UTQzULKywaBZKJc2xp5ee3uGRi8YCfjh+sS1IhbPkI8AwYe6L8apc9B7QP4EgLQuPmxTMBMKhV3rCZfJWVged1Q1ZBgiftEkkp+Ehv6CmiEqpB9aarAjSiANFCCsF16G0RtGd7Xnuu06HpPiBcQfHrbZ0Ct40NLZ/Qlzg\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14013","langCode":"vi","question":"mnCbKjXg3CBy1OZ5Dfpghi6J7vEWzaPWPV+2J++vh1/3QhFuBXw2eFCC9PITRvf94B7/OUawkaNqvg568qGtPSkFHMw+lzLI9YJKFW7r4SFoYbWNpcAXS7+anfg8lHj8","answers":["but","as","although","until"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE61ftBAwZpDkRZUe/mOj2lFUKB2VHL4/sAacx5z6k8yZJ52C92fgZDFhmIl/cBHRt9HZy0mmdvmm92k0dS6QB5Q4TQqFHqD9uTpRywZb0J59FiU+e18DkcVzqCZJQncpkHjjC9EU3ci9Jn+1q/t86MPefKtmd9P1EReQkIOlR2GEC3t4w+yZCIFpSMaAJjNT5K+rWxuQpKMwduRc4NxKhcxpVOym524OHi7XncVoiBmdduIgq9g+Ww0CS5rl9ns89gHeTylUdjXkz4U2HzAeJ8hBYC5fa4BPAEadaZwRiMdp2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb7PrXrjGtk5EAtiH6BH+pvDwHeM2f2TuUURNxPF5SfKtuZ6RyY8fhDgUkgpO1vdq2yjdpJHc22/RSH8GH1o47W/Yp20XPVJA3h7+6LVF4NFXHcTYlvutuKx+FNaOw1Njp6gYLqfvo2qIgccOPkIaZn5nN33Bt5fvg50dXmvLwGth/UF4fCT/mxeH+0XN8QNZpGRj75Ua8jGn939pqixJgiT3cMTkZfWkoqU9FAIF8A/SwvjXGAh4rbTs7V4ZpK3YfYczJHcB4HMMdcj8oy+caLtnfTfziUXpDxERBU/s5ZOVOJgZiRJc+EGvuUlCAGe+TcjYXLpQ2XXFKRRiYqaWACXc14v1bruDVtGfSHdnrNpUvSAwnC/E/HS1Va6cJFlhSYlbp0dKapGAysd/I7N8Mliz2lKxZfVvs/1WdA8xEUqEjGUwOo7r/k2u7REhvWFGLxKfcahWhMDMx4lwU6LzdVCVkDhLbSAQwJLbJeFVkfbHOtEiteKI2pf2i1DisuP9yUlRR6OI88lDDNKSErtrfZghxuBHttJLoYMEgHC4L29XPjfhtbJplalK6foCAeYV2A\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14014","langCode":"vi","question":"ROdWncgL+h38kdQao3V1d7W7CX35Ospgas4OnEs/u/UM6RbQDiiqAgoaVN6xBVcP","answers":["or","when","although","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9Zgb55rSwyQ6mnEOMFGHeA9C+ZutoINMirJO9e/jA0J86UJvWvmrNnS9R9aWDMbxRt8Dk0Je/5XTYEW/ZdhEv2FpAap2gjDGWvGDyCHNbJceQT+bZOflfc9vbGLGdYD3YAA1vxBMZyBXGTtG/GshSivjcDZQYTMpYlUDIGHKPMhUKK4xvZ2z/OnBjkYR9uJgwGgpobcnLLcIDvwZ7Od/WKbQNfHk7e0xLD2osbH+F6mQNuSjRXae9XVGENernP0Bs8ygWrH4XqVQxBfW0viWdRoP78uezynm/w0567Soux0SARTxe2x1A5pX4UaVzH5SXqaFwb6Ucj0VK6w+gnZzg8FAjX/9/AJdCIw0GcApMoonIwDWUXrsqaspXj8toAMHqnhVeXYOTPNvzOiun2vbRA04F1YlzQwyQAc1DS0r5wX45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/O+YKhI8AJuohLM/a8o45ceWUPBsMYVjAtvsp3ja5kceN2sUZtQYM8LrpT2ga97MYAO9pAknfV7XpDB0xHMCvYnA9pFkWSL7JZq6Bpz7cWEY+tJC9DRYvcVgRitKTF2ba6M8U3/xRGBCyfJ5VnBgCzBdJ5oKKWMVkldqgLo8fYKa7/D5EbWi4mfCusiciJFu74IHNWUVEeyzE4Z/EFxRpNRo68hcCrXjlibKeiDtIEHOW4GscbQUQeZywYoImkq8JLpu9Sqc5Y4q5JR1MQlBS9HnS/XwOVQ9odxn57dFPZrOA7ONQHOoB/7seSD6OdwzeGcJORiFKXYNV1sBEUWf4BGnTyWkSFf6VjwspoKAyIEUVuGaTcrxZ44++UBc5YMRBBiGo+KvQddNRFSep8RG/DAqQkwTNjsduWnELn7VO+PG6Y+Q0ORi95f8onh6lo+z43KG3aq5ZicOZgqU53093oIzpbWYJcM8z17XZLbpG5Mfc3WRri0WEeHLAl3RSrohkhmfaQ4zaBy4Ikxkz9xQhe8\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14015","langCode":"vi","question":"NzBV6uxp7xbmh0FJGUhccZoZj78wuZrpr/d8NFoHu39pyA705WsttuSb1UAd8OOs4kHw6SOWlEz4Drep+7sMHzTj+e0yW0u8My0lJ2Do41M\u003d","answers":["yet","where","so","when"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+SxEbEg5DchXqXFOXrU4so8HzWM2gr4fiK69CmjZPUamEmIQT6WWQs2Wv7eIAeqSanDq7RPoJdTESjfd/k0khFV5R/0Sp+giSv/OGhxjWYX4+UYjlodFGd7qvV9XMj0cqF7RPzHVxvSJjJkzpkxKBzenjwD3O1TyuuShKSPca5624ohuCRwll64TAGhYu+yqCZvKZ2AaTzQSYS8DK8h2Wa0QPieVaDa4umV19z8bfWllPQvHgmTAxpo6YOYNLz98LlvEltKsIDu1fMJYgpQMcOjNoIDkmj8+RJ+gFZR2tzRiCBczsDsddplUkL4R48Ag2cDltJmLH+ddTPU3hNdHMRlteIZV7yMgAr6nqARcteEHHb9IK/HBehldXD8sTHW+zG0wRu3p9BVJtT9Qmju/s3XhVHaPOin9jr3QyTMBkTJUOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmrZsKOuRol5ap+70NOfkmMEjUZMZ5xye9a6O7YZURHb+JtIt+/TJ+0fzzdTeatp96veFzfWAQL2c5E7gRchUgD9udlfpt9rqBc7XFsHy51knA4POPL0MyELHgrN2/45oInLkOIBgIN/AzEKjX3L+MXR0xbH5qLLxWHIlyO7nKusxC8fOF7sHKp+zDI9upWFxAGzKEmjMGiy1tl8T5uaYxc9OIZgvGDiCQFeToV80RmMuIZi9+2NxIFLn9D2KuJ4V1bThGZBSS2R8+ykSsw4KfN0WqV4geJvHkZP9RIWoccCWJWKnjDu++K7aGH6FH4PGoCk2ZmXEhEXlkm4U3N6ol7WihQfVI1c4AJnG8DhtFvu9wXA4qyXq/FOHlCI7Msy/lCYBz/z0Z7kb1oAgQ2eXkdOwyNobulqXydpgNXORT5NgIA+eXolwINY14IYvwPGCmV7er/9cxPROJ8moN4goWCiyA6fWLwnVquKzmr1pDtyD9m8DhoFWOY39jpMCJ9zLN9ubU53S0XGdMkPV9cwo5uWRv/OItFzjwOjoHY1TesQrui6wHCNSd7Wl0ZFB04dtWrHZOzCgn6CNYSc0mZBvZJMSNrO3fZXCbfji+p2hnI9bZxOMMSX5q8AXqGlF9Sd3b+Sy4KVC/Y6iPYIpnM9w92DDAU7CjC+AW/gTIAqnehdrb21V/SOwc2v5oDr0q2/HsGlubk0P7/gSjhDpszwbWI0aJz+A3d7b21SGvl9yRjg8cLWU0IcyYp4Dk15oN4m6b1kBU6b4qZmkAwK7FQ0M8GVxu7urFOa3Q+t9d9fFnVIedYY25umixjbOcgU9EnvNaqHwHw5o/iWHaSbmeROduOyuq+GJzPW+k9Z2TIlkdhEF+yQMDuImb9VfLdih4gU9jyWBmWPHPQjDwppOu5C/3Mg"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14016","langCode":"vi","question":"4DeBGFWQ/YXZEzAGqfiFpeEWm3L2ppImeLqI/MCPKl9cGyKLG4/jh+7k/6tCOPA1cDQ2qA2DxxOIs6UqBglqjcZ7Q33VIJ53mNTm8jlRGnI\u003d","answers":["for","as","as if","although"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5qinf9I+AZK9rHHyHdL9JOmNZUuLDqLV1DpJehHwXqHkr+TzGZCcE+cZ+GgXQxXbc5455HiE8hMzZxyPnd0IByv8+WnZIKXwKqo54tewr0IOFoNRTQxbJia0UmcqQafb9uuv2LQcmREbt1rllETSBgDT13Va6Jxcf/JquW3+O0nFeZ52QP91XZMz8y6p087zxKIjGIaN8bNQbN3FjJDQvbmZqCa441W1U1+R1lPIpWghrVcLVmjvaBIZXKxcTqw9PXXZVnGlx6ObMStyaBJQdBySyXVXXVumumGh5jJHr4+UOQUf8r7OUlewfxrN2jOrceck84pN7OED5FVlqxAEmr2NuWDlZEbTrwi22H7KGI2ooiRzaEjfuvMTBuOb672WnBf/MmdmrstpmJEqkrMNTLlrYbC0PAvH/VD3UcJKaUZFf4kmkIGm4uUz+/MqcmLER7zhHLwljDqKFFvnd/Ko2/y+aQJzo+l0jBGzppRy8dNB2eFMnzPVNgRthRchf/Bb4jt6OMXT63W7CPPmK3hVDh+l/JLX/TwjfLAskbxBHgc0IGjNFvo2mm7zbxzz5QgimNmM1frDgTna1hb20NZmZvlsfbsMDe0/dGMyT82ujiK4ZAP1J7B+aTAQEL6F7LCO163ybAFXhjukk/h/0x0uzaF8GgTle2ybEhfkw8a6B+alVN/y4iPZlW8mlROtvplDKFvHVEsth8uLp0odGn9zgf8VlJki8cPYtBlQpuCt4e6VTwj5gAeuO6Wct6YOXR5FfNhfPJJIRm4woDmu6iT6eLiBdfGx7yJQU1I6Ya15bNmi/2x7znIpqZcXqIG1MzGO2UG1bQHpPuY0q6LL0pM7HzdJsjAvbKvvvwBtfVuRlkLraZhg4YRuVfJR0jD24uebSjCdJLdq+mBwYXebOL504Plf/ZqF9IpmKKmeOL7jgmU"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14017","langCode":"vi","question":"jKDa+AAicF5cDbYq8ggC++XsKkNXr9G2yJxiydgggWELMQzACvnZdtQgaWrOPL7i","answers":["yet","as though","as","before"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9EsIEjAaZWTXK3ZhiNhwXM5oODVqWmTKuYSOuSvlcDrBzIh51K4d9pBsIwWMytp4/uAqgpPBc9xUar9D9Imr40QNmgRBSrDsOAN2binXUu41iZGcXTkmJvXfYroQE1DSTvrt9Qd0ii1r7OJsmIKl39aF8SDDZt2diVfyCTNgE9B7tGKsh6FYdWhCM6//TWhyDZ7DNWhZo1NeEIywidDEAgVBHgacFZ7OoCcno97Uk/PZit8hjoGhK4jOenoqA02o1SYZLMmSogeb1HXuvCBAYvezluGjXfqo62anbpQRDAsh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8XBqpQyHFDKMAGwvRoQVY4K8hpEI+FHV1SSFxRerggsaQxNxuOfcL/hCMQ7Cy7bjM91us3g26o3Ccvf1boOyijUQPDbB9xc9s02lhAyPbFC6xgdwCFUEMIimwC1UYMRbHr32YOmkdyrtZ2MdU06E2XmmXokdzM9DZuVlIQv0x/O7uc/fVaXj3AAQg4Pni5R4XXpb05ICnzdJ2xrLKCG7Rh3NO+5vjrjYLQwBBLbC06ZQoC1yJ6c9KOlG8k+w2Mz7Kk7g179JVpDc9Dy7WTd3/bYwpY4l1TfCEKB3xM2Za2+E9DISDye2Es4hgk87BcPNSuiYqr4MJzupPG/PyXJTGzUTvoFMrqmu3MHEn16h0EZvak1LISDXgf92AAA48F7VnC8dwGeX1lbTEWwHtopSe/dB+kARgFzxTBobYClKIlxEXw0LdZYOlIGuvWaSEbOFCuMOpa0VpCD3a5NS3dCJh/ju6KsmSslEPmylRTHIkZsh1xKIxg5+qYaZTlyVesgz4T5PBgts+f+okmKcdNzIAcV"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14018","langCode":"vi","question":"kwsdZb0IPd0c6uHHdfFh9nEaSG/6UPCYTXsQliYUwJ8c4TCfUCCGpU/32st0+9Zyzfzl4gyeI6fmsGPjGcoHdQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["as if","after","as long as","because"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4BO5g+AL0F0j3DePr3xlogcTY1iEzxRZvk90hTWl1bd84/PMzM44sur4vlCn1CpTjIUTqJEO7righuZfo8elHI8BzhZRYGY0392ZoBDGRtYBfhcFruExLGiYjsLXmV3iX10HI5Wf9XJ6Q3ms0CP2my4InaziAXbwiC047zuw1XVZwy+C9/jcLrCMX49Na3O4ohXYHu3wLn0lUe/M126ID/Jrl4nGOgbrjvgvho3l3x10183NUEJDCpLdVawfFd0B1pn9QS3pCBPUu1H2ROz1SECamXCkCffY4d3Y4lDlJQ/O0ZEUJdRHbMP0IwFhIb95uRDt23pp6RCo4dzaKXF9wGiWI50pGvqlYxq08AfxxanUpp03ewde6HpuBSOVBY0PnN9RptHEDtVlFeDPsRMgIOX3X+/nfgd9ZxXJoZZNW5MqKVsMyuxl8p1FbFRS+7ofRCl3qmQPQaCLwt685NPBFwFha8wU3LmOgkmsePkEkvifnsr2AMpdxmFa1fH2BThmtCrzbaHedmK7j+hgra+2JxxoAXAHAxj/uaQcK5EAGbUKDO0e9L2yNh8RGtJCS2bpEEqan5W4OVZShXGLWotkKXJmMHSLjP0rSAT7qOiAfE0tED4nlWg2uLpldfc/G31pfPtXQTiRazy0OG7+Rv3zkME41iJfz0HKuGG1wMEnJuWT+QFM7aXxzPvs5mqLxXyTcMlD9N2AoB1FJQj+PkPY9cT35FUDsXxML0Ojqs6dgaHndx3/3mkyr3Y8aX4rukyRVve8GXfFn9QfkphnP4aS9/urzjQ9s5InLnLxpNe989L+4CqCk8Fz3FRqv0P0iavjRA2aBEFKsOw4A3ZuKddS7jWJkZxdOSYm9d9iuhATUNJO+u31B3SKLWvs4myYgqXf1oXxIMNm3Z2JV/IJM2AT0Hu0YqyHoVh1aEIzr/9NaHINnsM1aFmjU14QjLCJ0MQCBUEeBpwVns6gJyej3tST89mK3yGOgaEriM56eioDTajVJhksyZKiB5vUde68IEBi23FR7gPh+CQrMy622N/xQc\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14019","langCode":"vi","question":"I274LV2KvWgGta6L6nmsMUIO0cmyt487pX8TRcCHnBGglNPMg4/TVkFYvkQtLV0ONQ0D7WGPeagcVAnToeV8IQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["as if","after","so long as","before"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6+H0vG6Dc/PKDsveN9opcF3MuzLZZtfk600D6aFfMjl84/PMzM44sur4vlCn1CpThnrWdvtR2jqO/wbaSllCtnA6ur4OhZKLBj3O+cB8NQLGB3AIVQQwiKbALVRgxFsejPaQoCvbMgwazYlq06wq5deYWIBvXeDCQf5GLqOxx/k45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/KPTsUaWbeexuPVYj7wiw3L1vgPmTXVmbu0b4C3c3i8g28nYHYiDP/81tmKsFKl2upy6/qNpqE6zz06jO5s1hDbVTdt94vn2TcNJIiN7WJKEGfwZGzrmUZS0jWkvcgH4Qvgxa2KvbgnnX9DRV31uQS33GgSv0LrdRFZsqYGISPbM6LrAcI1J3taXRkUHTh21asdyn1rT7rUzXbjt1FWB40futCrYniiLTaDul7Hu4TH8BC5szUaJWef5AuF9kXpBlFd5StZSI/SFC1+nqMxzCCfgfCfgCgHkUfTX6mk5GmE7fYrAQoiWB0skmbcItqw1pwzIETclicz5jGcFXk2WHMedSMIGXU4KLQiUFI0dsrIBn1pAy6LwkbkiVxbYnq7C4bXxZQyuogm/zdaDbkaF/67OBwEDNdI2hWr0UAP7mF0K7he7S5eaUQEM1H8zGOYHcYUowysyuCHDJWE1T9NruWIvxDi7sjEqLLLPHQt2yWLwn/LMhHu0N8GHd0mFGeDjSdsXuh/fbd4q6XAQvuolCbebuQOPDxiJqksNoTKCqPfhmohod7Qs1ShBtlFCw+p6dH3f8zAZBizb2f3zeYPCodsLe3jD7JkIgWlIxoAmM1Pkl0zQ+yHig/mdRpQAxTbgeBNtpVCu+xDu8zZWra09XOEBoKaG3Jyy3CA78Geznf1i/QlkrLBmPs3vfwFIHbe8yFNoIM6GnrBSanLNfAPwVeMh8SHxqN6I+TUg0W8vFOdIcThQnHENzXGZJKXzRYDXjqgYLqfvo2qIgccOPkIaZn7NtZApDOTp19o1/XIs12LQ63k/j3/NGJkP0fFgmo/QMCxf6hKgcVngPtLRdzo8yDyvzcEz5ZC9iSKMqFlgl6O9JoRpwOOiL5U2F8+YU0qyJw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14020","langCode":"vi","question":"jUaK8qnB4jebS/f/rnmrSNfcajPAmd6dIF4n4+EnnPaWJc6/lMcsrFqpxmV74uVlenbcM66GJnV0jKeP/3Xrrg\u003d\u003d","answers":["because","until","although","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+HTSYFsWRpP2MbqwbXVprQiqfJHuAj/6ICD+MZztx3+I+WDlMZ5pNjFXrbXHSxBuxPfkVQOxfEwvQ6Oqzp2Boed3Hf/eaTKvdjxpfiu6TJFVtNx/B1njwB8YD0ENYv7HInRORLhMybR/ysyl4Fgl+OYFQcc4vw00yLm/QXD7o14aOZg43LMtOPS9gbod0ihUx4R+1IXbp784fuSEjxt/aT3nlQ0i2FUBFTMpx5080JvzlE6y1QA5RI+oC5BPvQ5pjJR7XZEAUTISV/LfH3wD4VAa3ZwiVRO/rbkggK4REqxG6Ku8pMPP9mY71FFGpXrQhnPsrXbixFhpDhYRLkAObTYNjpvJRsXYrmnLs8kkhdv0F9eshkEIlSPe5hy8xrcEhl51vN97toc5I9iE1LTdiEAhifH60z1jT7vt+9ePF34/8r0MGyec4uSeZptxLUwvbcvkmRnxFdK58zDGhMaHOJL9JCp8aBFYODueMmygsdJE9+RVA7F8TC9Do6rOnYGhx0xPbAdO64QRPSvoW9mpEc1eetPdeeyHnHYxe9YUxbZRv/OItFzjwOjoHY1TesQrui6wHCNSd7Wl0ZFB04dtWrHZOzCgn6CNYSc0mZBvZJMSNrO3fZXCbfji+p2hnI9bZxOMMSX5q8AXqGlF9Sd3b+Sy4KVC/Y6iPYIpnM9w92DDAU7CjC+AW/gTIAqnehdrb21V/SOwc2v5oDr0q2/HsGlubk0P7/gSjhDpszwbWI0um71KpzljirklHUxCUFL0edL9fA5VD2h3Gfnt0U9ms4Ds41Ac6gH/ux5IPo53DN4Zwk5GIUpdg1XWwERRZ/gEadPJaRIV/pWPCymgoDIgRRW4ZpNyvFnjj75QFzlgxEEGIaj4q9B101EVJ6nxEb8MCpCTBM2Ox25acQuftU748bpj5DQ5GL3l/yieHqWj7PjcobdqrlmJw5mCpTnfT3egjOltZglwzzPXtdktukbkx9zdZGuLRYR4csCXdFKuiGSGZ9pDjNoHLgiTGTP3FCF7w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14021","langCode":"vi","question":"VGaSbA10lKsmA7zu8dcOhYisvdAGEUt27LkXFJIbm7nede9o7/OTyQzNGzm+aVNt5vk+NhIJupUmsVedT8ms+g\u003d\u003d","answers":["as soon as","till","although","for"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE3mmgLtXSQe7sH5iEq2IEl5yCMcFYPlKoBZqUUGPp49PgPAASoaDIXi48B5JmQtW6hVgV8KXNehu/1y7o626xkpJUUejiPPJQwzSkhK7a32YIcbgR7bSS6GDBIBwuC9vV2oyIGd91+hesiuMQTpNd9tQ5BR/yvs5SV7B/Gs3aM6tx5yTzik3s4QPkVWWrEASagjapRim+i8hZlPAVRodltTss4NXlLNSO3R5rBp1eflhyN5u3RTIR64DjAjSKTdzI+pUINuZucbp2zKqTftDbnbZF7vf6a07O4TkW+mHbIAAAlmQl9IhFah7h6g2Oh0paV+uC4VObzbeQvH2hHsiXBMVoUKtSQ4unSQ8fjyNrEpr//hhPWs3LFnPPRqRa8rzahR2wax/T1bHBWDNFfumpfEiBAr3+hBhEVB2x8nV6K+VMLqXR5iPzZ3v+uU44i6ASEBlg+O28K8ldI35FODCF6EQYBJ7ACh0SBMuNyPmkWIDzkrx+vnnlYJQOkWTIEysEh/88LhHDYuB5aEveQ4SEth0EjdYq+P1/bj49gBmzEee1eFGWpbWWT1EcV96Debw7BlZEQOLzM4EZkn27eIIoE/NgbQQbMrhuD9l3SyLuZqRAaCmhtycstwgO/Bns539YvZ3dT1O3B3QxdPDSJ3vz074h9s1nqRYff6Tt0qwA0KMTBSovxKwLxWnH+p6ksu310ZdIWA+A34yJ8yrJDv/eAmC3VS8xxNGcL6TDdBgD17/TT0IsGNkJ8Xz9WQHXSN+fLVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14022","langCode":"vi","question":"1oQeovAOIe/Twlrgs+v5fAE45MCsiTGSwY8n5yupXxSSHUiAq3rz6j+r5q5QKbRXfuZklZu9t1YXroi5ML7jZgMnbFU+Ut5gHec7j4vmXyo\u003d","answers":["even if","yet","so","but"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE7we6ml41U7XErOQNasOwn+Uek/97sftBJmZa8Pzjd+2U2ocIvaIrBQpQQfB4ztEdfOlCb1r5qzZ0vUfWlgzG8Xk+HUi12sQkzvd2TdW05AQkWI3ZtqzZ7lLd0ujGuGkc2T8Tgb2qnYca/70E8SwsQleYWIBvXeDCQf5GLqOxx/k45wDr4aPlaZwDEs+vyF0/KPTsUaWbeexuPVYj7wiw3IUdRKDKyHeR1Tpadgd988kzliD+2QdeMC1KBS1pILVI2UyTOHnnB0RcFCjT3qXu9emEauq3qvNYEv7XzkqC/ZsGkX/zp/lsRnSpKVvs/1QtwbJB7Z3wI5qb6G/3jltfk618WUMrqIJv83Wg25Ghf+ujHejwyb7gd3dOLqVdvUxj3qrehiUXKIAiWsMvV4uyQY/zZQ0IJJOthu3xDmzsVLRiiI39Qft1L+7Vdvke5+k6cUOVcUCl6P7rLaeEOUl+GFVpv51QDCAI3f5kuhP/rv8Msz8OiJk1vhM9MSzbt7nStVEbO+gtiVhrDZPr+QiSiOngwjVmysWdLBxVfbjvO+z9Bu5hrPcbN3ltVnqXrtAh6ek8RiaO52p+xHPX7DJXPDuRzfXZ4imrMUmEtGMetRmJ4LNxLWG3WYzfE/aft32AbQbNWoaSZ6ZFY7Q0NcBfJB0IsOrThIdVwUn9w6gETYlXfgaHjdCEJtgFT37kefoPr87MPgjrqOhQxIar3xM/d+xWq5WftLkjbVxoPll7lZW56iP7gHQpsLJDItdroYLIoFge5nYQQNo+JGlPuN2L2e1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14023","langCode":"vi","question":"so+N1VqZ1tcSSJ08n9EHbtiprWcqQ2Qf+gXwTvvziXitBeQv85CeEI4yrkGEwIz8iwTN9aC1jc8ZLTmN3NRCfg\u003d\u003d","answers":["though","but","because","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE6XSZgQ2MndZX9QIpfW9MLc5guSnVnWHUzDP7pFEdLMHu5Lt+Quk/j2zBI373SMcM5/ig816byVai7M8bJYke7024bbKnL8cwJF/G617wKzFqIAbZqlR8gwviX+h4WUGoWhKrBVlpJXoiq/2Fc6dUKAuez2AnemWLnWk0qcwY1Ffh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8WPV3OmMg5TkcKux6zndgbS8Tb/YRnPXg3Z64k/FARy4lcXWmMulY1lOYiHBMD2J0JBAIdDPUuTPnHx4wH+jTF6YuaoofX+WPhgB0ERpBpHRb6EDB50NNNomZZjKxHVwe9ET3aRgM1ovnQjJxfDIdn4+oGg1hJxwJlrFL8UImGpy8nVTvHJHkej+r2thqU3BaAKGbC0x6IrWclVrgxcm4jhEnSqAZUWmkVm/dyuCq5AjjklFyEDVphklBu4HxPExcnfmmAFVI3sILxW5lcfw8ZAsmVl6X3jzZ20vnoON0B/Ms8uPArQjNpEwgL+UvaLlWxCUWJyGoCKhm900Iy2FnB4MI3I8DSWJ2ymNrXdPZ+qvODJOlrNNISKU13NH3XfZhv+najozTfT7Ac44SCiE9XlLx84Xuwcqn7MMj26lYXEAa6su62aAfJwVsS7nwsBbLkOFPE+NNI0WTTLARGqqJp9femPR0zWvOQ4UTBw8CZCqrFBxZVvqgwFpOHglaMy3YCmPRw3EzUr6GI350u6yk/viEN/wFKKBO3PC8C7U9djVsIccflJooTfAWZMgLaiQS21rGEVvzDRf5Js9JsXJJzTaT2AaGreKdntwlIqeEKlrFsq1N7c0tsOETo7gOfvjWYEOzj0PPTeqjkEHNljkLW+2xdcpFwC1rzgAiq3cnvblA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14024","langCode":"vi","question":"KV51xbxvSXOGfjRFpU2ZeVM+4J6gNnR65+oNwLHI1tApjVdN7z+izV1GcUvNxoKAbtvdk1jYh4Qo/1Te6UGSJf+04+jI/Ut4dP0uYCYLqMY\u003d","answers":["as","whereas","until","when"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeExEmavins8/Kg1L5RxSbvnAA+ZacZrO/1bqTThCbijrsEbhvpFt9Pg0V0+jzwm9KPxqLdOEQmgUr66F2gWSL8ra18WUMrqIJv83Wg25Ghf+ut5Go5rHLFWXFqKSyXhQD1tkmj0jxnDEec6R6uwPsCku62b5Ui0O8Ulc9rY4PbOgSMGAHAzr6aZaE/svQSnlLphCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HONeXHtLLLJljzlYBHFubIvs1VDnPx0loYyOHynMagm2allWwaRKhrZWvr/EB4UTmqvStYWLaN6pjo9rPTSivJL+Z2EdgLW+rUnUhI26qgSpx57Aim1O7x2ZSPFr1DAmRl/peynX9c0U1inPB4M4j32fkVm8GH3pXp+tIJX3Tk5AtbcpQu49NJeVVGDTSUDELJUGB3AIVQQwiKbALVRgxFsenTavWgLWD87Hfaoc7CsCrUGKQM/O7CkqAk/xMh6k4U/HvOEcvCWMOooUW+d38qjb/L5pAnOj6XSMEbOmlHLx00HZ4UyfM9U2BG2FFyF/8FvGxMmP8/R1Uw10qvKzZXUV1/8n9SoQbBmfI3Zz9e1ZN6Q+bzYD37y+hSyiPheda7BBkhYVH1xxEjrkEiriglxb6wMUpMoihTNef/PX4jZDx+IUjf6IqWgKps/8oB4BqNq99Q0Bw0+yHPyp4F1bZlLeY19LVtH6Q93S/PUEO5i5/4ZWREDi8zOBGZJ9u3iCKBPooz7ZEuBeibZ5kh1I9SujDOltZglwzzPXtdktukbkx+eNv+MNwnEtSgh2Dc/NaawXuQpC0MZeA4giEqJ7RxxSUF30blOnWQ0wmjOR9BTL8EF2NOm1QtFLZ8f2/+Ka08vuHC0wQdDOydQkqEu/IriDRbpA3gRttikZqg7tq/KD6HQKdk+yT+Jna5R+/OQxjFJZlMZDa7s+D3cxDrw6PeJsToDz8asByDbN+3wxbaJqkfavxiIFJjzXypKg4fa1d6y"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14025","langCode":"vi","question":"t9c0bQc7t7R/ZmGZSKk34R0vwJrgcTFQ17KfYKXlaV72tCkJjaWMFJx7fpFDiu9JXSKhgWTV/PdchdEEM0D8BA\u003d\u003d","answers":["before","whereas","when","but"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9Zgb55rSwyQ6mnEOMFGHeBadtz4PuUpGtLdFPd3rlLDtfFlDK6iCb/N1oNuRoX/rreRqOaxyxVlxaiksl4UA9ZyhzF8/v63G+eHxIDSb6SJJXUqs0N+wOLEU9CMKE3Il1Z7ryb7T5r4/sCda+ECfQ8QbO0TZh4K28wvruu9ARkDKpZfRgd9/jtX2hDbd3EqCr8c4kXbZMbILblL2WUJpwUc3k9iCZY7rDPOfa06hqZLAyNV3Od5bvGozgS0J69PL9NuyTqXtg6qN0Im1P6cEWCSr0GamJA6utbq9eowrBaAR8hg8jT48mz+Aepv4XXZvyiewzWtYkaaHa1pE6OoTSvmDxuph5WwaGP0hTXJ5z6MbZvaj7yk7FYiRX3QBjopQBgWVGtYCI8rLeZLBX29W64QqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjTBcZm4yfO6pr0wpCzBQ+cz9Na3fzwhu/YfitqlUkqf1IWSyRqbKKfnLfjZXKarEbJvsJLWVwsjvtdhQqdFq/Mp4JUdcdDpbh+hiFc9h+FeKGzFT1eA4mHq4/CtIphYiMxWhQq1JDi6dJDx+PI2sSmv/+GE9azcsWc89GpFryvNqHqX4L3lHH6DIm4lOmJpPvos1as/nZkwCglaHQ2lprL8ngtWkWTCiyov+YLgXNu7UBbyfkB8iv/dRISxbE+fYqUF1TYVyYhOlQM3aCR41zeeiEk7tcLnzC5h9ixuWQVMnAAndDglu4gC8WosQn827tsJ+jYM6ccYk47FXBVfYpqpJUUejiPPJQwzSkhK7a32Y/sMUDqCsP8FgnMOkSNmtZYs7nprBkHwVPjBl/K73DLHHepkI2JX4J+m/ISiFXgooJJhhl1QGQeP3r9+cJr4154RvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14026","langCode":"vi","question":"GqBHTv0XBnBU7zlu4rZS8/O9MlvZDhKPqZYCa4xO9niyXEWADj+lnKCKo10RicbIOWJR2lwUus63j8Ngx6n8xk+G/lXu/ybOXbVZiwB6vhyfHrXUo/7IbhRgiixYtxFa","answers":["while","after","when","as"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5ooYbB4SzrEkcXMQcVRQCeLePaAP+UK4UdNAgEYH+FeLx84Xuwcqn7MMj26lYXEAbMoSaMwaLLW2XxPm5pjFz2WsAznlwJNe9uPnAmJPqFH24kBW/WRac3cuPzGNE6lGiaEg7KE1KwLdqRpAcDMh7atgzIbTDFN5PoZbg5msQYx4f0ZN6/YAOsxnTOfeMgiVU9Ah8qecHeege06DrXEsOCN8QSfk3uBAqW+/Dl0FtWr8PxIRruIj1yg3E6lEAt4Sgu2McMcz6s3aXPuYx/E/v0D2fdLcTNl0PSirqewDklbwLGwFU4q3G9r3p1tiS19xOJz7fjlYmB1FB8VOZvAz3XWf+PQ+q81qsZKhrHgpof2hWaCjf8NWOwUoSYkhrn7WBzhgyOT9fuNYJc9yjrylf3t6gs54uEg3DUUPtGlv4KjFkKHXYvqnd9TAQtDOs3UsIshNN8CCkLK9b3s9nRLQYUZSs6DI2v0jXKd5EBUpfFZZWEbxSBNsoX/hzxVTZXwmrNbiGzYDXlk/u6ihvpeFeM8XDrbGhaISZQdEPQJXpfqgNo+zdoN2XkcLP5pA6IOSxPfkVQOxfEwvQ6Oqzp2BocdMT2wHTuuEET0r6FvZqRHfjVsW7mwzHjB6b5Sdh9zDaXF0SBWfxUoPBY02wRncodHryfbQhg19uhfKuvrYHElmXLEJixyomlhGw3us1bWClaFFnh7ACOmcJhTzezY1YuQfjNMDbIwV+c1TVCVPylisA9TdgAd8zu2eZiE3aVJNEzqU0SgBaWHfs5DWh/s4QUMq6HgMYsv0Bc80n+PNITlPhQdV0qW6FgDFXf8n1jvHgiiA/KFx7t95vCU55MOude3YioZN5KFxhJRKz0+kYGDV69tRogH1077kI6THQVV4IcpypJtb68ZfY6N7iNOmHs5DJJ0pWQGPMEgBv0yRt6U5EO3bemnpEKjh3NopcX3AaJYjnSka+qVjGrTwB/HFqdSmnTd7B17oem4FI5UFjQ+c31Gm0cQO1WUV4M+xEyAg5fdf7+d+B31nFcmhlk1bkyopWwzK7GXynUVsVFL7uh9EKXeqZA9BoIvC3rzk08EXAWFrzBTcuY6CSax4+QSS+J+eyvYAyl3GYVrV8fYFOGa0KvNtod52YruP6GCtr7YnHGgBcAcDGP+5pBwrkQAZtQoM7R70vbI2HxEa0kJLZukQSpqflbg5VlKFcYtai2QpcmYwdIuM/StIBPuo6IB8TS0QPieVaDa4umV19z8bfWl8+1dBOJFrPLQ4bv5G/fOQwTjWIl/PQcq4YbXAwScm5YnyQimGp5QJ62ACKM7SoGW"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14027","langCode":"vi","question":"x3oValem6oqP4m6pRcfns8o5vUEBpCehpl/oP4J/9/9iyVjzSrQUObItm5FJi77QHGOkp2Q5DLm7QS/hFT4fhWDckuCzLtLHPPdgn6pSdi8\u003d","answers":["when","until","whereas","since"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4M4PGGKgu04wlPXAFoUuC23AGEelpvdTN32sWEWLG0pNIM/Ch4NTLQWtm7c/+kTih7zhHLwljDqKFFvnd/Ko297ybbBi69wRyX6L3jzdGnJ6bvPPHUJC7Qg20nV5VhphRCoVI4MWGgl+NwFR9/tvQEZZfoowCXvo7orSAPr1HON3w2c2WcXxRSVvE6mYLCvFpRDI4WH/5/IssyY9HefCG7UL3o+n0EYMh8hCkuKCpncdjr/9Ig/pqTZuiceNU4xgTBC0y7fNPSQuCcaNfv/HK0N5VtTFGrvHnFaUMQbnzxrq2tlgVME7L0mjcG6AZlYNBWhQq1JDi6dJDx+PI2sSmv/+GE9azcsWc89GpFryvNq3aT/HJkeY3996VFF6iNIBVh6D08ag50KpMQaO8/OvxnS35rGxOHemqppOcscrELxu0xEX1izQ3Na5G3TqeQDRg1qXRp30yx2tbXSO2sgWJ8sT97u08CtkNhUwzMhxmSpeVT12M0VTlhw9WqIdroM88+i/U71amyUSCmerPQg0N2E2jpDaG0qQlrijAjr2A+y/Tlcrhz7bvk265xB4hTaMO9BhkYQeizpVIPeRVXYJK9ImwYdznRSUi8N/l6U7m0faIl3iGrJDxKJzdW6LHElwWj7pHmmcjoyeGe5I8DP0MVwMmlYYithDqwcW9V7NYLv1+nYQ6N1FQaPLEZr4JvcY8PRy2AG2j6g8mGaEb9/8beDyubiogUckKdkWAnB77PgflCvvM+9vi+zWbKmGvPDJQmqRNpUw88CD3nUOG5B4uUJfcV55P6GV0h2V4VLlYGNv1HbDz/uAKLGXx6UogSWZ5NIn6PJFeeCo8CJvMNdre0D8fBp4fHE1+R6M/NHMR4A+tJC9DRYvcVgRitKTF2ba2Gmj6O1VMnQDnsGmS4diOG4detHACAGRu0ijJXaSnbL"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14028","langCode":"vi","question":"GUJZXHYYTvr/NI2i4lg54cVES3Y4rsv1lyxUP1ODESa73y9JqXlq4sFoX+rav81rJR4uv+jRjmBUH9OpwU3v6QVUD9i7DyUxl8AAjRL74p8\u003d","answers":["neither/nor","either/or","not only/but also","so...that"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE9UYXJBmCZIee92mvduIbyKfhjzG4nYtKSF02gTYmv3faf3b9NI1B2+LKrEJEGrZLLXxZQyuogm/zdaDbkaF/64E44mzOTK00zai48ZFhF2X/QMqCwE0ezBm56YPrH1k4kwthHGcybedFRBndF/eGQLXArGkboomRHMV3TBXwxwKNOBdWJc0MMkAHNQ0tK+cF+OcA6+Gj5WmcAxLPr8hdPwOFTSbkeumGewdO2bG+8CD+Lf8hZmciRqlO7vO6qG3R58oizBjTnpr2Ah7Ym/+QhRA0c28NINedV5qYmcd6hwkxAeCHWDgO0R/7IzKCPOwFJiEBY0FbdhNWu4IxzdsxgWsFn8AU5sC8HSHA3XZ2LSo3XVlIvzE6czE3qcQdslHSGB+LCGsVVkm8chQFADTbZWiUlI431qai/V54VXo16dHLF0PDOLbHiTzUnNadowKs3VbknTUU+ULlP8gJbr3F2VQrc4kQugr1vyUyYRDbX/BPsaUfX29xhfA3D+lPQ6HbUGyLVNI5thsxj2LnDLNCdLysquoaUucjw9N53nXQVbL0qTHnIQntC6/tUsmUJGMM9cgzXFXbMkXDcxnignDC+Zru52UocSo41pSw2DHq/XuZncltMN5Z81sVEewuZA92Gs99CnL1DJWbtdOMAftRFkAObTBKpztbxFybmiRQsQASVFHo4jzyUMM0pISu2t9mK/fAsQbf/q6aL6GNGk0DSg\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14029","langCode":"vi","question":"5KM2mgkv8CNVLLJTLxjY7zibAQHI5Q6zNCxBH6aOuXIbjebX5DlJtXNfNyHC/4rfyLTec06FoZMdi5FKD6FQCA\u003d\u003d","answers":["so/that","neither/nor","not only/but also","either/or"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0UXUBpbIsTft39has0AZTkm6P/pYYtdTfiDjgLjVXjAQ160tPUldf1Nqb080LGveElRR6OI88lDDNKSErtrfZi5erU05tnnOT6/UCRaFCWfbJNuAiXOZouGMuoK0PPowkW0r7UpmnssjlBK1lW1Utw0IEB5DILA4HWQG+9Ux4cWh/hv42ByxzWSLbHRi5Er6R/awcaTQeWsihKCqqJle8VTuSCzVNTz40LaOIXQt2O26BC9Po3a1tUY3XOumRScgOo2nSFbHGQ82mjjg6h1A7UeyQcK9ikJ//woFhnEmWdV4kzu15Vlp2YRYtSBoCu2p/Q19cDyxJ6+FMewMdRz3mg2Q9DCoh+0durCr5pJuHQeASE6HXnKOfWDNe9lQUoojb95bxCwk/asDY0Z7SxwPERM6oA/k0iVpfLF8ICzthQlb78e0Yzd1rYqKxAkbfjlx9tGUKETzN/wnlDEES+K+1VTI3rxSL3IZzJgtLT/48Dt1+6SRiRTcSp2xXFiVDprrjrLqueH8rjli3xg9B7aj+618WUMrqIJv83Wg25Ghf+uBOOJszkytNM2ouPGRYRdl/0DKgsBNHswZuemD6x9ZOJMLYRxnMm3nRUQZ3Rf3hkC1wKxpG6KJkRzFd0wV8McCqOeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14030","langCode":"vi","question":"IFaR/zHCjqKdg4yNiGPjhHyISAHL1tYMdqdtJmS1Y2QWaxLirUp3jYyshj/x3ULZ+53nDBP1DEwdiE3acv0PbA\u003d\u003d","answers":["rather/than","not only/but also","neither/nor","either/or"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0u1qIMaiOKtXATY2DzA95aoZZ2uG4rZq0oMQDOHzjxsNnCAMZUwJVlvw42eWJpFKK6uBkhEQky06dyUMAtCjp360kL0NFi9xWBGK0pMXZtrRrAT1WOzfkFj/hfR4ODu3BtIuWcVLA0qPjGrvq+B2PjsKVFNKIldooe+AtBy5HWvlBoY5ZPF0Ku8V8kqzYEp8l5hYgG9d4MJB/kYuo7HH+TjnAOvho+VpnAMSz6/IXT8cme/lMqztEsqrtsdR7CtSTP5rQJ/QdzYvs27lZseHw/Dq7s49nJmiYMpP4uD+4EIqxAwohHg3GqfNehUn/QhZKomGAvT31ErByqA/M//LhJDVSbVkoICFHPlfVkEbejBsmSKiBzNw1QmEZbYGOK5AKJSUjjfWpqL9XnhVejXp0csXQ8M4tseJPNSc1p2jAqzdVuSdNRT5QuU/yAluvcXZVCtziRC6CvW/JTJhENtf8ETxgQKdlICYjf+27mIL+8XOsuq54fyuOWLfGD0HtqP7rXxZQyuogm/zdaDbkaF/64E44mzOTK00zai48ZFhF2X/QMqCwE0ezBm56YPrH1k4kwthHGcybedFRBndF/eGQLXArGkboomRHMV3TBXwxwKOxDUiFv/T4Oc/iqhI8amDgHMmthKHd/RuAvG2Gmzm9DzNSMyyGRtxsBk6qON8i8kGB3AIVQQwiKbALVRgxFset0gz40l6kPLwsR4L5vVhlk\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14031","langCode":"vi","question":"2Q2V0Af82fl82C59VLqoA5IRgkb6j1HxZ3eXf9FLehbffMP43yHCXxcx3XxIeUWAhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["neither/nor","rather/than","not only/but also","either/or"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE2jYWHC0qTxmp88E8cOn/yEvIlN7Bqyy3WMz/NkgTX19MtssMaE/qnLKUhHVaf5kewJBEP/XKVa+rrGbI6U9ESdURqP2ziWju0+pELGs54NZJCDWz2Y5ZP4UF0XjA4SdCcyfXR/SueYjsG6s+M4mis/AXq+uLXJHpwwLWUljQLu1dYRSxqWgjjMLtF87C4ST8bWVlbPowC9WwbXUE8cHwUY7nnJRbiFTPZsyZOddO3tS4/eXLypvCfPROrvKFA2NBiWQQFgGRKfKXlGBpSOmxzkH36EqVC1Oo9PV2R/IGaycjA796QayP064EBz8FnPxREhcHHJrGp8cBDmytyphrh7xcY8ub7boR8lrFXZEoQ6IHvOEcvCWMOooUW+d38qjb7EKSHzgU+FE27BA1bwGjrlbPDnPk6yKQLLkp45XuJoqwH9ZwlZe2T662xYrCuRniUbQ+D4ejWqGW2ayR7ts9zfnwo7IHhQ3gH8wt+vscik/5QExzpvtlDh8RBfNSakb3j24SOlqMjZRJ3i3V9xkJ7JIs9MJEqe0z4P7PSQfvFAo71OZAPOy9RZdtVBvI/ckS6/1k9UC9RIBM+jVV6O1ZkaelrmwazXMgRm+b1E+ClQ5Cm42JBfE3lb1YGAgC8J0WhPfkVQOxfEwvQ6Oqzp2BocmLmIwSQZZpEE23BPe/BauxqktgEzKGY5SxiWhmxRmqrTvv7QBlj40QM80ou+HsFIsLhXQmfPaZcIMawgfnRypYupwOpZVIlMsqY5EbXiSyA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14032","langCode":"vi","question":"ZwrQqOTM6Kgxwc9ZECi5qQIu/DIl3V/6O4cmyq0EDiRNSJQQy0HfTaRPqPjTFt4OhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["not only/but also","neither/nor","rather/than","no sooner/than"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QOrUlkh+lnEhirN4mphEWevWZw0Np5yrbnlrr2vyCVcgg5uqv0+Cz4nm/7RXCeWTd1wqdKymnVQlR0UjVJfCUabvYQXMAe5AKpMD7FCiwqRLhr40R9wXgfnx06gIpW2QKXZvafibwK6pPtYc6dGl03mDvTHhjBbDOY/S4bVEDLC+kBcihnCJspviR+XWM+/42gCw+f81W1+Bglv2ezO0Qu2XKMKcnf+DjUXuLdo3X0I+yAuJvlaA5k4qKYBd7mcYf4b+Ngcsc1ki2x0YuRK+kf2sHGk0HlrIoSgqqiZXvFFEFzvQD53Y8Brj0u3nEh1udbdIbSDACW7CD5Vd4mg10X35lnSzPxodZLd+85hyM0oUtTlOmgZ4nO1vkUl1+aNBoUvx7hZvzSll2dZ+ag7lk7a1RERvFibJqmPd7QFVD6JyfX2Ge0nhUd7y2/3w0G2CQg1s9mOWT+FBdF4wOEnQl7Pkufx8wqXoulyrYbGFOpVcTmaemGvAgTYvgkbhAD8NTq9+GhO0ACQJBxrdGp2gpqLXWF3DHckpzCkhdSnP7GOsuq54fyuOWLfGD0HtqP7rXxZQyuogm/zdaDbkaF/64E44mzOTK00zai48ZFhF2XyxIvXJMQlwy0wgqXfbarYUwthHGcybedFRBndF/eGQLXArGkboomRHMV3TBXwxwKOxDUiFv/T4Oc/iqhI8amDgHMmthKHd/RuAvG2Gmzm9DzNSMyyGRtxsBk6qON8i8kGB3AIVQQwiKbALVRgxFset0gz40l6kPLwsR4L5vVhlk\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14033","langCode":"vi","question":"T1b9VAKK6rfOHxbOVE/1yNvTVhWnC+2RLZneZqr7RUfLqHcoQbmUrN0qMhOJOfZN","answers":["neither/nor","either/or","hardly/when","not only/but also"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8blRuc0YEIyI7VdcHILOxBFnq3sPVS0WLtVhNYD8zIV9Eb2D9+UfFMHIX2IIXmQHbJmtUje2dCwJ/xwv7v4OUFJUUejiPPJQwzSkhK7a32YIcbgR7bSS6GDBIBwuC9vV7fGrs717yw03IJ3JkhHOSny42dsuuKZrJn3krU0bhdZXdfLk5Ht181eTeJXNZ8UQGfVZIzW0ExycoXxN341Q31g1ERE/zqLUZNoDyPkYbolCCF4zF33NKgT0PVf8F8W7BLH0vcMK8s4A5mopgJKaNNi7gPcVEW8D1MjRo7jcelHiHVdJDR0xGVHeIbUJQQHmslDUqARCRd+fcfs6Lb7mDfj/p0ZzueZj9tRGZx+nbeNrRwX3xPvijjm6STsNFAL8jh1JOczJpF67YYuxIpJEMz0xj+Afdr/cDhWu690VbeHFaFCrUkOLp0kPH48jaxKa+QyDpjR1dCurfJQR40GG7g0pe+N5Yn1ZxFEXkPyVV4cJtl290hH1PeWfvfQvYR62NtZhQ879FYIdyXim3eqZ+pUl78qwVPSUd4Y0yab+czNngs+izj0ipnzrdL7yJ8s4klRR6OI88lDDNKSErtrfZggEXYHDLsShCa6dwNRaJiVlrgvJWjNrWC3Bxa1kAt7RSf8V/uS8ra6WoYBDKpIzVRCZRuLdASLQdyVVzJ1vJpM"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14034","langCode":"vi","question":"buHE6fB/8P1spCtGkKZeLgrjn+79E3eP9Or9PiQskIhYgJolEDAXkhYFdpdMwExwJwSP+IzsbfVDRkdZP1cgNlSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["either/or","not only/but also","hardly/when","neither/nor"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE8blRuc0YEIyI7VdcHILOxBFnq3sPVS0WLtVhNYD8zIV9Eb2D9+UfFMHIX2IIXmQHbJmtUje2dCwJ/xwv7v4OUFJUUejiPPJQwzSkhK7a32YIcbgR7bSS6GDBIBwuC9vV7fGrs717yw03IJ3JkhHOSny42dsuuKZrJn3krU0bhdZXdfLk5Ht181eTeJXNZ8UQC/cUcGaN+s4Cehy4kv/IHPN0U14JN728t5atrgCqy/HqAVHpLnHoYIiEBRQNj/pYwMeZJ2+cu/MC0AElMXVJSwFineqEc1l1a5E/i/u0IRwayShbE/+DyNAaslVj01I1uzq+i+6tmBlKS4CQcCXH1lN6cAaHqctnPzcr9QwFcVSjLW0Sk0edwCnZb+NhZqK77uhH7bRrw6x/jAfffreyltBbNJSJp1bTVgNJENFlhuZVGAWXv9/iRYOkntVQM7HIBPfkVQOxfEwvQ6Oqzp2BocDS+q+q9ZGzRiUaeeSqb9v8zEoPh8F8qud88H5A6RaqASD0j5W4KZm7eh0GwHWNmV1W5J01FPlC5T/ICW69xdlj+Yna3b04m+a+iQHVcjqZbySRZgbM0DnZu5tF75E7YGthmjb0+sTDOP7p8x1y8tHGtfyrTJVeHGvRVT8TGlgvdIbwTGheGTc/sjxVJrCkXLVmtXMaka4Mqd6MidavmCGLY1t2x59u3u6O2tZ2e1oJago2sTv8zamB2pd3hmD2avynnU1PTcsC+lTldA+QkBgCgbDP8xtiipkPklkKLEErQvwvYfrUWinCte7f+kAQ9Pp4dPdFbf9CVyM4t2yOduWpxZKlt18ZYuCEdw3jtn76LhfohHb7aJX123JRDffHfU\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14035","langCode":"vi","question":"0dfQ9JkovsTMGDZR9+hHQOvCnSaCHt/it4EbKvCP4zY26sh/yTIpMoLE06xOqs1HPlBQluXtu2KM1a7whsr1dJkcbpviGeTHSz6j8klorpQ\u003d","answers":["rather/than","not only/but also","neither/nor","either/or"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0u1qIMaiOKtXATY2DzA95aoZZ2uG4rZq0oMQDOHzjxsNnCAMZUwJVlvw42eWJpFKK6uBkhEQky06dyUMAtCjp360kL0NFi9xWBGK0pMXZtrRrAT1WOzfkFj/hfR4ODu3Pp/3dyDnWI8UMXLt7xwbm3sKVFNKIldooe+AtBy5HWvlBoY5ZPF0Ku8V8kqzYEp8l5hYgG9d4MJB/kYuo7HH+TjnAOvho+VpnAMSz6/IXT875gqEjwAm6iEsz9ryjjlx0cytJl68siiTzLAJjHq0hzW8RP4UKfQCWekOb0ybXlQwXx8UAFw4aru+ZsIXiT/CPLZpj5cx48txXHrriTBG5cNlIu0WhBAkhhZIE6Zja73GcLRuhv/GiNkiVyrYF9ze6lv/D5f+TFZleHgcTQT8RYhos9PgCqjGP22JxtiNSpx1rJT/zV1Tl5hiBD5NAxDl3/3gvtU3NdZ3ravr6ap/IpIvZOool2kjN6mpSwIoMN3fxaWnwWZitsYcIkv26rlTctza/hSj6Ug7Sv81MT732mw4Bm6eVLcOAVp6vDJtaA0GEwRofHvx3OSkt4nOYHV4tjmYXu73JUaBG5JhxAHqkhJLfQIlTZlU2dpiJ06IBYjQXVNhXJiE6VAzdoJHjXN5+2guogInpEQ9F2v8y0z3/zfQiYITMZZ2icb2+gRHtDTDxDCGwqlk4dsaI8fkk22ddotcFpsdFQKbBvQ5bgSmYFPRfh31sXiVD5QmaIDSsQhrYZo29PrEwzj+6fMdcvLR2cfAXGE1cK4DSfINi+jd47DzDM1zWaLlzyEVk64s+5qvTpnAavSVdVgIcnjOL3pUlHywuHNWVPzp6H9zYTEXWfV8GYkeY0SAB81f2gLtm+euKcnmrOPK8PSPrNjvG8PgURPdpGAzWi+dCMnF8Mh2fiw21vCcoMMoZ+tdaT3RQtVKdX6/1ODSyB/rJQjL6Fyww\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14036","langCode":"vi","question":"MPDfx8UgbCPapRTfIhTsFQFqO6swQR67eyWi+m9RGUvSzhAa02uji9WVZPpOXPKNdkeAYiLDJF+Bg1mqDLQua+J1vSS44TcBf4oNAoNrYmI\u003d","answers":["but","yet","or","so that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEy2mGF5OIcAkQLgdimAt30OkRJ7Z6c+DFWNY+Rfjc/zkN3XCp0rKadVCVHRSNUl8JZttkdCVyVBHYu6vgenRjU2Tp5ENzFxg0EGYjg209Y++wF6vri1yR6cMC1lJY0C7tXWEUsaloI4zC7RfOwuEk/FI3rqxbE+DZ7gx9gaYL3AwFe4ce7JYN4UsoVgo5rElRJ8xmqMXR27X4cHRzO5vHhhAAcEDeSLeA5PgVoLwQ900zHcUeL3RtHhzx/PWT/SmqJ10NFFlNS2wFojD6frOuU2IdV0kNHTEZUd4htQlBAeaIHaqNH+XVQqzmsQMPHeS/4svhMZiqTEuIAiJRUBARgSL4kb2re+aJJ/pfoN0MQDcgXb0ZHo3tXRq02wmhl1S5WQFTpvipmaQDArsVDQzwZXG7u6sU5rdD631318WdUh51hjbm6aLGNs5yBT0Se81qprV/okKPGc282xmbIAZIxDNPNFicWaBIc/XYLVqyd01TM/1NKwQT9gWmVrwajWrbrggahqX+LgvP1hxsq0QI1Xbdtg5T5w6Z9AOODfUhT862jZMp6q237nrzpB96dQs/Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14037","langCode":"vi","question":"YVhf2+tUxQMupYI/8LFX9znimrZSGWU6/P9OC4iu/Gfr+ecRzy3JBh2MfeFMiQz134JS5T/N1NRtkVZP0W7JNyXYdW94xJozx0XVoNLnxyBKYj5G/T5+mjqh6hIr7E3LKMvrzxK/nOA9a3ImxsgcSQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["not only/but also","neither/nor","scarcely/when","rather/than"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzwm0Q/A9odxd1hpcq/6Yzu+sl/AUEkL+KHsYMwo2QfFwxDzy4b/rw8be/uwh3ChMriA6NfWrVTFb8BbxS9GrpMe84Ry8JYw6ihRb53fyqNvH2v0jrg12KMuznZTpqDG3TTGAOpHndgpZ77GH9Rs+lUQqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjUabJMFRTVrSWehqVjE21cGFgEq8U63D4QczlVl2rPtgOBkWZuNEEEHFg1VOfIQGguufmAFkmv+BlHvq4z269QcLv7fxpSfLHfwUUbFadrHqJOzpTCB6D3R4YAD5o3uwYpiQv6KUYzUXRAIsftnYpvHHq/xE5TVZRIjzR4qA2Xoh8rKrqGlLnI8PTed510FWy9Kkx5yEJ7Quv7VLJlCRjDNdSqba9PPxH+OPgAlVrAV9a7udlKHEqONaUsNgx6v17mZ3JbTDeWfNbFRHsLmQPdjcVNAyrJ42Ybr8teVcTSuS3zmGQiAy2L6TudayKciCvhWhQq1JDi6dJDx+PI2sSmtF5ruNrvV6roS0NpiJ8kBTN56nhlQvUccpGimhdIvc9qLidBjwWimu4MdX7eAyl+ZhfMd5TvlU1qOjcWHjV/UZcsxZBoGc3c/WgYrRG0KlUeez9mhvhSyRpXAc0V26nxQid9E1iVnHi+f/kg1q5SgWSVFHo4jzyUMM0pISu2t9mO+vbG7Qjz+lK1cLO9iIHeE\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14038","langCode":"vi","question":"mi1R5SeWyvJAun0E6fjtvLrnld8alfRsfhkaCDfqoDMTqIWPBc2vrfF2lf/9/WzkBhSmLSlrsvw+m1bE1WWTrFJpIdl81eUck5vHE0wqIYo\u003d","answers":["scarcely/when","neither/nor","not only/but also","rather/than"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzwm0Q/A9odxd1hpcq/6Yzu+sl/AUEkL+KHsYMwo2QfFwxDzy4b/rw8be/uwh3ChMriA6NfWrVTFb8BbxS9GrpMe84Ry8JYw6ihRb53fyqNvH2v0jrg12KMuznZTpqDG3TTGAOpHndgpZ77GH9Rs+lUQqFSODFhoJfjcBUff7b0BGWX6KMAl76O6K0gD69RzjYjmCUVDf2eGE9s96UiRdMZVhsE66gXyay6dk0Srtmyt5RMoYVq/y/J2V5QjS4aK8eMSkrZ5/sWGcNxgomvi4OId/ton3zTDInE6JOpEyQSoO2tUREbxYmyapj3e0BVQ+icn19hntJ4VHe8tv98NBtgkINbPZjlk/hQXReMDhJ0JJ15v9lAybzohZfABKbDEJVXE5mnphrwIE2L4JG4QA/DU6vfhoTtAAkCQca3RqdoKai11hdwx3JKcwpIXUpz+xjrLqueH8rjli3xg9B7aj+618WUMrqIJv83Wg25Ghf+uBOOJszkytNM2ouPGRYRdl/0DKgsBNHswZuemD6x9ZOJMLYRxnMm3nRUQZ3Rf3hkC1wKxpG6KJkRzFd0wV8McCjsQ1Ihb/0+DnP4qoSPGpg4BzJrYSh3f0bgLxthps5vQ8zUjMshkbcbAZOqjjfIvJBgdwCFUEMIimwC1UYMRbHrdIM+NJepDy8LEeC+b1YZZ"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14039","langCode":"vi","question":"GMugKu5OQqvA+1+/o4lLTfpqHZV9n7fus2n8WvZY6uE3XoIZNQRuaYDzteHw+ykPKKi0ZxKOOUN8VCkVYDnQgCTJooiv7UsxRd8Bsm0GCTLDMorISXplCY/wGUOSrTPd","answers":["no sooner/than","rather/than","neither/nor","not only/but also"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE4QOrUlkh+lnEhirN4mphEWevWZw0Np5yrbnlrr2vyCVcgg5uqv0+Cz4nm/7RXCeWTd1wqdKymnVQlR0UjVJfCUabvYQXMAe5AKpMD7FCiwqRLhr40R9wXgfnx06gIpW2QKXZvafibwK6pPtYc6dGl03mDvTHhjBbDOY/S4bVEDLC+kBcihnCJspviR+XWM+/42gCw+f81W1+Bglv2ezO0Qu2XKMKcnf+DjUXuLdo3X0I+yAuJvlaA5k4qKYBd7mcYf4b+Ngcsc1ki2x0YuRK+kf2sHGk0HlrIoSgqqiZXvFFEFzvQD53Y8Brj0u3nEh1gmqgTq2zqz8cFAd/EwBWe5Q57zpa2ubo7Rwt6GxZKdw21hOEFabHY+LoNcaxV5YAUJUWhX8w2xHVUWnl4rWqolJso3zVGYLS+ln0JAM6fz9s//yvYu+4+j0PO2gulMNSc+bqB0v6aFncdy/EJQw54mPLLyfdbnVhKgj45yxZXrzSVFHo4jzyUMM0pISu2t9mMslsITtzrAjz148AHdOb0fjepqrh4vT6s/J+MHp0ZrAWGb1ngOKgyXNsMpjzqMiYeTdlS5NgiojSijJ3pOTV03EFKvfVpPAYg0KGYCj50DgYu4D3FRFvA9TI0aO43HpR8T/Fak4qy4MfoDmngvw9fAFbhLT/vY4GWd0jykigXzInKeHIQEKVPrO0ekPB/2Z39uu8JccOznjBspYg9Sfub7gKanQ1WZK3hSj7yMa0A1B64DSJgqqvmnLVsFrA4nBFAL62jLxSHbw7Ca+d3OMdQUe84Ry8JYw6ihRb53fyqNvRRYxvw3YQVvwLYcjfrc3QKl1NXjg8u+M/F/iL5daWX4\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14040","langCode":"vi","question":"8gYZozxXkK6BhtJ+QjRjg3iv7ouAfYhpnSDEHUy35WCUyzrlA4c3/1hEHQNMXO2o+ijSS7Bgmu67WG5w7PLk5A\u003d\u003d","answers":["once","although","until","where"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEx1FZGiCp6G1alhU5bup0LDJk6NxG+T9BVS2yNQyBhzZBh2PaN7hzkfgu/zANgWclPrSQvQ0WL3FYEYrSkxdm2uA2BI8dnLdRgLZImPIyRC6YT+tzIU1NN95eoMUhmQI3slGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQLxvr6fceM+yyazyYf0zBOarTq+XceOd/AwULqPxfdbxeCIR//OwicVgHrr/f0xvTBY7AINHaEewtToJ3rfTTSk35brhVl1boGcNgiZ6JCU0VS5gwrBfpKL2hGGdIlTPq4wlqtg5MxEgdmm+x5fZfeUOqsDfCWm3yNhITFWOq0bj0NfXA8sSevhTHsDHUc95oflCvvM+9vi+zWbKmGvPDJWG41nsIaf5gqFeupVHflr6I1x8JIuSp4aC9UXJbQiMjpeAXRm4JL64zOEABPKWx+hF1Q4MR2KKBUaKV/7koacEabvYQXMAe5AKpMD7FCiwqRLhr40R9wXgfnx06gIpW2b491s9hPyBa2uie5MYKXbSf4oPNem8lWouzPGyWJHu9NuG2ypy/HMCRfxute8CsxaiAG2apUfIML4l/oeFlBqFoSqwVZaSV6Iqv9hXOnVCg7/ZVXc+ySW6ty/O9LcCH5yiNilZUwkmjnHXDcStg8AbyXTgYRZyuNZ7BMqhUDb4AEsWlgJHOK+eTjgnul4pX6axwl1BcMQaGlngoGj/PzRcVNxp6Pn5pNQvE/sxhgu4VC4ncitnQeQuUmFieMVYODP5L7XwNNXuL8/0/vOszbp0\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14041","langCode":"vi","question":"6YzGs/EEx0AgOE37V16H0GctMvmKrx25bAe6AKQrJ84AP/W8CDZgV/FLpgguW8nUxM5qQE7uuXvTWTe+NQAZsJc1jH8mkUN8gjqAWfiQyw8\u003d","answers":["yet","but","or","in order that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE06IRFpCb4lcBsJDOIl7mhGDt6XdR2OSAYLn56StaWBDyHBDzyMLmGOpBO1oCO1i+hWhQq1JDi6dJDx+PI2sSmt054wJvw98vf80Dv3WSlrtnqz3aaP6pCpmEg4O+3mZJG92BR3p1oZ9TwKvLqJz30xkibxB1zgGy2EBpFBK6JEyEErBNGSbuj3yLiPjL1BhieGnHZpC1zMONpAuv5Igv9qfpx9ZoVCgwlWZimdSdO7zk0LsKPW9sX4z1tv72QSrMfsjK3JVoV7ijCyVtGNDA1OE6Uf8ZE8i+zk9A1M97pr4rYZo29PrEwzj+6fMdcvLR9C6TBrYMW8gnPpMpm9YMzjBr8Tq8jiGXlG3KvQHxyn+HbDMNPIkM6D/zaOp1Zl9eVoFn4q2zRSytdvQKoEqErtXXyMzWDWRk5wf7QMmqQRRbChjrXKhuh84wm9ptPftyOS3LqsDKlzWJ0tgWHHa6C4AB9wZbU5Lb/T7/+KS1LQYMnzp0bJcjzKy7bmo118uUWDykWOhePm4mzDx+QI5QtzqeDBaaPHx/ld5gmkWmPuHUqorNVeFkowgHQOuWAtinGdUBQA0Um54Jm8Uibw440I\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14042","langCode":"vi","question":"cZH2FxRMeCrijrH7vaxjeVwzw0idVzK/TNceWN3iGO84YPa/itb3rI7T0/t3Sdv1TgNcd7kSDEixVkcP0qm7GFXicNyG9VXZMZi82XqW6DI\u003d","answers":["and","so","or","even though"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeEzJV0SUF0LH4hS2QSisnq49ajaTICrWjw7YBN5hL3U+ElrbGyWfK7mst/edrDB5js5DOLQS8mda9+wdPfAvD/TzMgZv0SzJ7W11c/tvVP4X1gGDaQMdo60AaS0xxzpjA+KYD8M9IF6htCXKXIQHjxLYvGSJ1imEUqpSw8AMM3+rjBt1V+LtNAkgG1MwPObjqSFELLicesdPchNwNPUN+t0ASxaWAkc4r55OOCe6XilfprHCXUFwxBoaWeCgaP8/NFxU3Gno+fmk1C8T+zGGC7hULidyK2dB5C5SYWJ4xVg4MG+jSnPhzsbl+TlkcjCvQcOr1Xc3CYC3oA8VLiJU8EP5ZTxORUAAHPXR2HP9h0LuJMU33utl9Y5ef7b8etEb/ev+SkmR45Db4PH1r9PRrZgWtPagBGQp6aK8gwSStNCb5XSqw9AAp+3z2gYpjH/qgSu23gqYnaXNnohX5kWJIP1ynMyZNMb7OipYfSblK3gWMkZKmHDOvUtr1vfeozFeYUm5/w1GKwKho/k3xuf6x3+A/smCIkNad7/w6E2Ed1LchTEK0f5srOcoN2DsqLBNHoVBi3ucX3/BcLD6IdEtNa2Q8+gJGuK4t1jwuei4kN7a6v4R3ipRd4NweAiUIn45VtFE3YKjSeqI+nmgfE6/PpNIuKpuAd94nVxJbAuhqLTPI2bPUvq3Y5Nh4gQa3zQnRBgsVZ0pJ68Blj0kE5dtiUUEWgHrM/vSISMfZv19dx8XDJdCVNf4io9WbcIPAFacf6XWbZimgyny6VIljzgejw02ltmKKLm1HLADENNT5aMtlOqkZJmp8qiicXAzYItGLUavlf5+cEywueJZ46hfYgKz3UbNzUWS0E2ClrP2H9/0Gqd89YMImO2lcfKZDQ6CFSOcGZP5JSIYyZ7MWPheNeh4/s4oUMjybBjvQUvz/yCEr1ZDMY45S8DRDJi9KnBkaMw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14043","langCode":"vi","question":"XHh8ZaTn8DinqjuDVrHMQpWOIJf0YQKCNH+ZPnhDOcEoxi5DZg1Zoj+9mxuUfy7lbx684i2YRXVQ7rT54PpIUWJiEzYRQf0qzvTQQUlhex8qcYojpGe2d9m1FVb8SSKf","answers":["such/that","rather/than","not only/but also","neither/nor"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE/eb5/Msph9q0xJ3mD0oi14qluFO2INRluJ1ENal+Hp3+Qc1oQyjoAMhawzkyaPKQrMXE8pCgRAs37V+m4nYdBV65HsSJwslUqsbRGeAqaE6flCvvM+9vi+zWbKmGvPDJe0QteVNBt2OMd5WYN9TEdrwYIuIQ4cHyLKvsoqgh8ctJSb0IDgBqJLCTvjFe7ps13vXECHAxB0ENlOMk6uv/3ZIDuIticGiMeEmE5ZLu4zhy9P7d7YJG6tWLI9hQEpss0jF4K9CSfY03adocPQYtrnUTZcRM15qsciwlGkBvV4OibmS1Wn9HQgY9KOsGYonZyxfGEJvTjpwg5zPZikq6nTeK8RQDE11+nni6hg9nnRN9MY/gH3a/3A4VruvdFW3hxWhQq1JDi6dJDx+PI2sSmvkMg6Y0dXQrq3yUEeNBhu4NKXvjeWJ9WcRRF5D8lVeHCbZdvdIR9T3ln730L2EetjbWYUPO/RWCHcl4pt3qmfqVJe/KsFT0lHeGNMmm/nMzZ4LPos49IqZ863S+8ifLOJJUUejiPPJQwzSkhK7a32YIBF2Bwy7EoQmuncDUWiYlZa4LyVoza1gtwcWtZALe0Un/Ff7kvK2ulqGAQyqSM1UeyNxo2CU1cCUAtlX/73u6xNRVYd9nfj5v45QVH21udav4WcokV0B8PTLTJ6NJ3R3EXVDgxHYooFRopX/uShpwc0KFCufoEifyleQdXYxcn7tJmoqrqb9rCUFdwyHbCG3"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14044","langCode":"vi","question":"8bPMfrCBhXNwWMU3syZrDYLtdmnC2kE7VUJEV511oGRGkzVv6Cx1My/5pPTYoAFFVCLMeFdHLQuamAL1RVXumQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["so","nor","until","in case"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+pcm1uHyoEVGuWHLlG01sYCb4DJxemCRRghp6AyjZ8aWXs9avJ01yCoMVxEYwySHKwFuek9cVXzjVWPAzKKFoIvw92ZizJeV1Encs8VN0AuGB3AIVQQwiKbALVRgxFsetoGNHel/RfwXSfdHDc7Jvdg1wWFLwnj8jjzjtr3/5FXUq0zL4jYjtvvcqEItiJskx7Wq1jPTbNXBS71N1ERqK0gCxjqwrzgQTZkxw0R/rykuCJ2s4gF28IgtOO87sNV1WcMvgvf43C6wjF+PTWtzuLscNIPlrjMbWaOFGrDteF7VRBeTn0ZzZM1lFJZQ7kS9Uo2uc0+xH55vVt/Wxbgjirfzt4Q5baxWUkJEenJz1gWEECA4n5qERAyAbBDmU5FNOz02wNd49HYZ/ozC/2P7KixQcWVb6oMBaTh4JWjMt2Apj0cNxM1K+hiN+dLuspP74hDf8BSigTtzwvAu1PXY1bCHHH5SaKE3wFmTIC2okEttaxhFb8w0X+SbPSbFySc02k9gGhq3inZ7cJSKnhCpaxbKtTe3NLbDhE6O4Dn741mBDs49Dz03qo5BBzZY5C1vsPxP9B1GKoaMPDJlykGUbZhPkTZv0YR7Sjn90bA7kwlgbIZWea+B1qRh23+kPXFP6nDq7RPoJdTESjfd/k0khHfnlqK8u7wky3aJtvidPNVyTk17S6sUsFQRr1qW/BnZJTqRgqzVLx0A9ccw/M2fTt90W1OFBZux+6qnKdlwiNrgbkI5bVyHXHk+QzJSo2rqGghUe13HxyQwsxsAech8eL3npT7SAwdYONrdWYNtopHDjJTITo/daXCrHoFZM2LoKOeRjIuj0ze0D4lZaA+lfs\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14045","langCode":"vi","question":"xOv/56pRrXqi/fWVealuEt8iLQDWxqQ6haTr1mZ9YDZ45+V/BdJNUriAM3p/0zcd46xti0QWxleWZn+LeX5g0w\u003d\u003d","answers":["until","so","nor","in the event that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5nYpzpygLh97ieLpnk64GmRJehvVHIO4/Lw5v9OKXgrkE9GiB81ndfTvvN2e384jV0SwFdEjr4b5D4lGTN8iZIRtek+4ll/VjD63NwSHR0KptWHOjP9Bmb2x+zRJPsNI62GaNvT6xMM4/unzHXLy0eNKWQF4DSyppBXhAfe5JkCygEKo7ONNxa4DW5hqBpRWaH/yiAOwN481vrW/JpPPskXqINdk4divifXsMSKbgmEPJdAMO/XEEf8F9iOI5KmyclGbHsz8/arAYerwWpS/15wfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQmfbCfOD2GZFAle9oed+TBDFin/ZWqP5HDcD29GLLQdgyvZj1Skm8LI5iZtl+ulEF6zkGWP0Sb/6GmeVcEk2TmjbNRcXfCXmGwZok4NE5UhdL6ICR4xETeh8e8BuqlF1AKbYzruChnzyZaBm5/Ds/RMU+Zh+mQg+rYfWWg8+gQqW+5FXiotP+qaG43qI4vpdOjubDPstE2Hg6vO0WSiTi+zPDRQKHvcSWgOmw9RLvfqTA6LIvHPobDaTV0/XPkY7ttLWHFVaLAFyVk394LHUCdK7qxq/Aau1Cusw0HQ+1TgKo74FZ+uGgYtHKsX0DjhLi6w/tQwmx44kn9RtfBIjSZ6XgF0ZuCS+uMzhAATylsfoRdUODEdiigVGilf+5KGnBGm72EFzAHuQCqTA+xQosKkS4a+NEfcF4H58dOoCKVtkh+Hk295UXsT53ZbbDraV7ElO6Cw2T2KYlpYTgdacJAZcbyMr8HgvX/kj+k8GyYbu9hPkJcDNfSt7/XMXLdkgsVB/sYlYyRbwX1m7ugm00LqUAysQ3yTy+FzkBtp3IifBtGIoO/HtaRJgvuwW4oMdC"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14046","langCode":"vi","question":"n53gTF+OPgbXxn/3MvGF8fkz7Z76Z+vJHPb+VeBixwYHl+VpeWxUS7V39aYmM4YHtLGoTFSkpc7mxDzKJrSVRTML0/gixbMkhj/yrr29GxQ\u003d","answers":["as long as","as if","after","now that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE0eA04bn0SS1abZ5jJMWSbUmWtAuPbyzDDnVgdxEaQ7OKhshcthRHl266g/nLZ2oGnrkexInCyVSqxtEZ4CpoTp+l/JLX/TwjfLAskbxBHgcb7jeSOpbfNzL2g+rIQyshsh5IRCxSbFiTxgfOEXTVyVwfMWnOOH9ywDaeeaUwKxQQij20q/ACrMBaDgPsZP7oFiOUUhfDLxZw9ymEorO9m4QYywhvv7bARZR89Cds405BCnkiU6Gy9Fw5cSD8Vb0fKEHkxXNEaJIUdFgj0qiZ3tB9GplFAeBKsPL26DYot35GCYktNGgeLjDjhHbvo9rhXNN5tSV+3flfMcEcHn9c54hyWpVCLjlfwfr+J7eOXHbgywm6IO1j41LlcYNsaHqCJvVLpCWOxqdMabE9ROWby55hJ9DKrxjxRStm0sPSnFPe6sFBoMcExXDP6NYGup0beRDt23pp6RCo4dzaKXF9wGiWI50pGvqlYxq08AfxxanUpp03ewde6HpuBSOVBY0PnN9RptHEDtVlFeDPsRMgIOX3X+/nfgd9ZxXJoZZNW5MqKVsMyuxl8p1FbFRS+7ofRCl3qmQPQaCLwt685NPBFwFha8wU3LmOgkmsePkEkvifnsr2AMpdxmFa1fH2BThmtCrzbaHedmK7j+hgra+2JxxoAXAHAxj/uaQcK5EAGbUKDO0e9L2yNh8RGtJCS2bpEEqan5W4OVZShXGLWotkKXJmMHSLjP0rSAT7qOiAfE0tED4nlWg2uLpldfc/G31pfPtXQTiRazy0OG7+Rv3zkME41iJfz0HKuGG1wMEnJuWxdCsqZ2Yvl3ltqmZkGSktWD0C4IZ8bW1uoDDNxzbc8R+fJVBv5vXt62K9XhXvqI9AjSkYbYNjXBqDCvxqGYzV0gWwp/bnOIHRe+9I9zxJdXp8dKi9C8IwifeUzisg9hj+DwgA6JGtWEBK8UJlhUkhO4QJ+tqaTsroPOQe12Ul7HigRIB28IHoj431HtxbxovHtAjosjhQOX/i0YhAcJKTQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14047","langCode":"vi","question":"CIcgmULYV+JLBhoRQeRnDf4DniWAtPV36ne1bf/1TBDLHcMhC9IPeq16djiNFGd+","answers":["so","although","but","after"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE5PoS3raCt2kO1k57+p6Yp3qpa+beWpeMVmeH+LuprtgrYZo29PrEwzj+6fMdcvLR9C6TBrYMW8gnPpMpm9YMzjBr8Tq8jiGXlG3KvQHxyn+XjzGODBVRe/pVmSfzTCPBFDkFH/K+zlJXsH8azdozq3HnJPOKTezhA+RVZasQBJqFYXlmFGqrlocnDfltu4YMkDtN2IxGpYArEIc1EIXHpshTRPEaC/H7iGsSmGV42dlgaHWspEgpdwPwk8DEIGT2MU+Zh+mQg+rYfWWg8+gQqW+5FXiotP+qaG43qI4vpdOjubDPstE2Hg6vO0WSiTi+zPDRQKHvcSWgOmw9RLvfqTA6LIvHPobDaTV0/XPkY7ttLWHFVaLAFyVk394LHUCdK7qxq/Aau1Cusw0HQ+1TgKo74FZ+uGgYtHKsX0DjhLifO5KxS7siCi2OxHm465LAfQ19cDyxJ6+FMewMdRz3mgzFhpXJbierry46uwtgdsamWilq6NS1zYq8iVUiHBmz+GzIzRJcDl+Rgkj77nI76OcyguGBk5OIdaJLQqtUYn7T/H6hI6g6tc5vJ5KZOwAvqJ75BgxWcQDyhp5YC+5Vm19Ckbm+BIuU08Cxrb0W2CdRAhVys25OA7xRH2zQzk2OL6XrpoJjX3jdtIYjfR8uMfpj5DQ5GL3l/yieHqWj7PjqDDwbxmg/OGV9yvB7vOJq7d1Jdv52IRSpJgleR+Wm3sVNxp6Pn5pNQvE/sxhgu4VOTFxgbvf5bVlm1VBPudTKYpoukXSdFxGuMlp/fJf8cI2OdLKGBywh/we23kmCZ239vs79+VK3++tjHS/wovsfh47iaz9CQlX9sMRAyZa9Ry1afwsGBsvyo3GHUe6Ymg/i5fs/NZFX/95lY2qS/3yLRF2Kc6Ww4FrcoeKlNC/HLjSpDQE2gFZP3a1wMW0x/adhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14048","langCode":"vi","question":"2HhL6UvKFUzfiN4dEELnkBLtU7PVY9kWJcBMda7qE/eT8z6xW++6j0dJLLnCem49bM7hLia4OUIVmPkK/e5InA\u003d\u003d","answers":["because","as if","as long as","after"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+HTSYFsWRpP2MbqwbXVprQiqfJHuAj/6ICD+MZztx3+I+WDlMZ5pNjFXrbXHSxBuxPfkVQOxfEwvQ6Oqzp2Boed3Hf/eaTKvdjxpfiu6TJFfPkTeojopZy+hCbqwis1Zof4b+Ngcsc1ki2x0YuRK+kf2sHGk0HlrIoSgqqiZXvFAd3xdlR4YOvqAPVXxqtrTqhd+W+VueY3B/f9xWPvDgx5z0cbdbzsWm9eZRfbzRTo3cI/fmUeUJyCTcvk+ZJyJu3wlSMZuxun2ZkSLMzd0DXt99pTpDEKVh5U97zsDX+DE9+RVA7F8TC9Do6rOnYGhy+jkI8JlFE3tEyrZ9B5thxu6he8hzrJ0rLavUQNNEEdVSRpWqJD9hMFAHvbeeNHEK/NwTPlkL2JIoyoWWCXo72Wo2S6JJYmo+WQSNOKgZFTBzBrqLhvSaowhWTm0kG5dF0rOcxh+8NU4xRGO39PmWxxLkJPzhcu+lhrouI+ZwG2r0M8FKoKxCY+gBatzimKCxlZEQOLzM4EZkn27eIIoE9WvYYlGvD16dkH50eS0nY7aLGnbDJaZIokwZ1hX4I/uzOltZglwzzPXtdktukbkx9rVMXCR6Dfi41yeL56V9jCT2KGnFa4XwcBS0cz4h2vfSV4UUJuuHrFsDfwJXTfJOY/SIDllvwEL6eoAaHNk4ncCqVlZQXNC5ew179uBWiqXSY+tk/eJY4/jJu/wMYTgYCuK0GO29SpPe9IImJ9WLucmYvxCokxp1xPTWKCIcS5B0oT276lrOMGj8KdaWsAXljNMbbVdiU85B+SJ0iHMdFsXhBSgL/wuVtJrtnJK3BVqKEQ4uAmCGWXMmtYoJ3R+ESd5+9T3y16novw/uebwTnWuL1hwwxG3zlP5N5AE6b2v+57n8yHZnF1Q55rwWeTeuIYHcAhVBDCIpsAtVGDEWx6M9pCgK9syDBrNiWrTrCrl7VVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14049","langCode":"vi","question":"uMQEAykPKuwi+vdwwCXk6PQYnaTDirttUcG9A6qA9L2ivSyYJN6MPHd04sHVR/hr","answers":["yet","so","for","or"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"n/ULZE9GCCEd537NauSeE+WdTJFeWbdpmHI+aAlOmC8YhsgxdNe8e8aXD28h9Tlzz3wH+Iczhsqp9RnxHcvCk3NT/8PQrQ0eQUXOoKyo6X3V89eh+wDQfhAyX8lM0x4VkIW1BxQaVvKllsdC2FkkdlaWfGZLIyQNXhzXH7rjWS0cS0lFLWuaPgdPWqelUZZ2ofPz7/uJbDLX3h1deLkBmci5zXrbT+sNYhY4wRgJg7xoehLzjB0LG/AgHdGQU/sH2DY6byUbF2K5py7PJJIXb3NFQXe+BV7pfUMmTMNWuehs7NvJyv5b8ykUjc4H4uCXyRJhOC0tmdNIKoI/vTaCa3TV1iE07plmxr97xx7dSIwYJ1gBmsIzGj7nRIInq/Aocqr/Hb2k/k+PyUzpmyh23sjHk2yorF32EiQrDnJV0+yXVZkgZ5CsLSTUXO2GRF3ULmJibYw3CcvpKMbb0utZbiFFjCDXpUMRKR5qvF0+TLO+tbbQTGjPswmlF0HRHbyV7vwp+nTeMUTwHNiNjW8BG0/DTrcsbgeDaBIVPztrQjX4wAN85+atFVzEg8LabT/JiIHTzSFidwO0tBKuKeitoWwoY61yobofOMJvabT37cjkty6rAypc1idLYFhx2uguWuRNSGzLElCjXGqZqnbVYJ6Is3YYsL9pgQpNzw6wzVASXMc4D7XMF565dzS8qhjcfQCB5Qw7UyIIVwAMgSVqxrVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"}]